<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-04T18:46:57</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018264197</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018264197</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-06-30</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="1">Application published</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>moll's</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>18</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кожа и имитация на кожа, както и стоки от тези материали, А именно кожени калъфи, Кожени шнурове, плетени, Кожени кутийки, Кожени подпруги, Чанти за документи [кожени изделия], Кожени портмонета, Кожени ремъци, Кожени подпруги, Кожени куфари, Кожени ремъци; Куфари и пътни чанти; Чадъри, слънчобрани и сарашки принадлежности; Куфари, чанти, портфейли и други изделия за пренасяне на багаж; Принадлежности и части за горепосочените стоки, включени в този клас.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kůže a imitace kůže a výrobky z těchto materiálů, Jmenovitě kožené řemeny, Kožené šňůrky, Kožené krabice, Kožené popruhy, Kožené aktovky, Kožené peněženky, Kožená vodítka, Kožené popruhy, Kožená zavazadla, Kožené lemovky; Kufry a cestovní tašky; Deštníky, slunečníky a sedlářské výrobky; Zavazadla, cestovní tašky, peněženky a ostatní tašky; Části a příslušenství pro uvedené zboží, zařazené do této třídy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Læder og læderimitationer samt varer fremstillet af disse materialer, Nemlig remme til soldaters udrustning, Læderliner, Kasser af læder, Gjorde af læder, Lædermapper, Læderpunge, Dyresnore af læder, Gjorde af læder, Læderkufferter, Lædersnører; Kufferter og rejsetasker; Paraplyer, parasoller og sadelmagervarer; Rejsetasker, tasker, tegnebøger og andre bæreposer; Dele og tilbehør til alle førnævnte varer, indeholdt i denne klasse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Leder und Lederimitation sowie Waren daraus, nämlich Lederzeug, Lederfäden, Lederboxen, Ledergurte, Ledermappen, Lederbeutel, Lederleinen, Lederriemen, Lederkoffer und Lederschnüre; Reise- und Handkoffer; Regenschirme, Sonnenschirme, Sattlerwaren; Gepäck, Taschen, Brieftaschen und andere Tragebehältnisse; Teile und Zubehör für alle vorgenannten Waren, soweit in dieser Klasse enthalten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δέρμα και απομιμήσεις δέρματος και είδη κατασκευασμένα από αυτά, Συγκεκριμένα δερμάτινα είδη, Νήματα δέρματος, Κουτιά από δέρμα, Δερμάτινα λουριά, Δερμάτινες θήκες, Δερμάτινα γυναικεία πορτοφόλια, Δερμάτινα λουριά συγκράτησης, Δερμάτινα λουριά, Δερμάτινες βαλίτσες, Κορδόνια (από δέρμα)· Κιβώτια [μπαούλα] και βαλίτσες ταξιδίου· Ομπρέλες, αλεξήλια και είδη σελοποιίας· Ταξιδιωτικές αποσκευές, τσάντες, πορτοφόλια και άλλα είδη μεταφοράς· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για το σύνολο των προαναφερόμενων ειδών, εφόσον περιλαμβάνονται στην παρούσα κλάση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Leather and imitations of leather and goods made therefrom, Namely straps for soldiers' equipment, Leather twist, Boxes made of leather, Girths of leather, Leather cases, Leather purses, Leather leashes, Girths of leather, Leather suitcases, Leather cord; Trunks and suitcases; Umbrellas, parasols, harness and saddlery; Luggage, bags, wallets and other carriers; Parts and accessories for all the aforesaid goods, included in this class.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cuero e imitaciones de cuero, artículos de estas materias, En concreto artículos de cuero, Hilos de cuero, Cajas de cuero, Cinchas de cuero, Fundas de cuero, Monederos de cuero, Correas de cuero para animales, Cinchas de cuero, Maletas de cuero, Cordones de cuero; Baúles y maletas; Paraguas, sombrillas y guarnicionería; Equipaje, bolsos, carteras y otros porta objetos; Partes y accesorios de todos estos productos, comprendidos en esta clase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nahk ja kunstnahk ja nendest valmistatud kaubad, Nimelt nahast kaubad, Nahknöör, nahkniit, nahast korrutatud nöör, Nahkkarbid, Nahast sadulavööd, Nahast mapid, karbid, toosid, Nahast rahakotid, Nahkrihmad, Nahast sadulavööd, Nahkkohvrid, Nahast paelad; Reisikohvrid; Vihmavarjud, päikesevarjud ja sadulsepatooted; Kohvrid, kotid, rahakotid ja muud sarnased kandmisvahendid; Eelnimetatud kaupade osad ja tarvikud, mis kuuluvad sellesse klassi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Nahka ja nahan jäljitelmät sekä niistä tehdyt tavarat, Nimittäin nahkatavarat, Nahkanyörit, Nahkarasiat, Remmit (Nahka -), Nahkakotelot, Nahkaiset kukkarot, Nahkataluttimet, Remmit (Nahka -), Nahkaiset matkalaukut, Punokset (Nahka -); Matka-arkut ja -laukut; Sateenvarjot, päivänvarjot ja satulavarusteet; Matkalaukut, laukut, lompakot ja muut kantimet; Kaikkien edellä mainittujen tavaroiden osat ja tarvikkeet tässä luokassa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cuir et imitations du cuir et produits en ces matières, À savoir articles de maroquinerie, Fils de cuir, Boîtes en cuir, Sangles de cuir, Étuis en cuir (porte documents), Porte-monnaie de cuir, Laisses, Sangles de cuir, Valises en cuir, Cordons en cuir; Malles et valises; Parapluies, parasols et sellerie; Bagages, sacs, portefeuilles et autres objets de transport; Pièces et accessoires de tous les produits précités, compris dans cette classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Koža i imitacije kože te proizvodi od navedenih materijala, Naime predmeti od kože, Kožne niti, Kožne kutije, Kožni remeni, Aktovke [kožni proizvodi], Torbice [kožna galanterija], Kožne vodilice, Kožni remeni, Kožni kovčezi, Vrpce [kožne]; Kovčezi i putne torbe; Kišobrani, suncobrani i sedlarski proizvodi; Kovčezi, torbe, novčanici i drugi proizvodi za nošenje; Dijelovi i oprema za sve prethodno spomenute proizvode ako su obuhvaćeni ovim razredom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Bőr és bőrutánzatok, valamint ezekből az anyagokból készült áruk, Nevezetesen bőrből készült dolgok, Bőrfonalak, Bőrdobozok, Szíjak bőrből, Bőrtáskák és bőrtokok, Bőr pénztárcák, Bőr pórázok, Szíjak bőrből, Bőrből készült bőröndök, Bőrszalagok, bőrzsinórok; Utazótáskák és bőröndök; Esernyők, napernyők és lószerszámok; Utazótáskák, bőröndök, tárcák és más hordozóeszközök; A fent említett áruk részei és tartozékai, amennyiben ebbe az osztályba tartoznak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cuoio e sue imitazioni e articoli in queste materie, Ovvero articoli di pelle, Fili di cuoio, Scatole in pelle, Cinghie di cuoio, Portadocumenti [prodotti in pelle], Borsellini in pelle, Guinzagli [in pelle], Cinghie di cuoio, Valigie in pelle, Cordoni in cuoio; Bauli e valigie; Ombrelli, ombrelloni e selleria; Valigie, borse, portafogli e contenitori portatili; Parti e accessori per tutti i suddetti articoli, compresi in questa classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Odos ir odų pakaitalai bei jų gaminiai, Būtent odiniai daiktai, Odiniai sukti siūlai, Odinės dėžės, Odinės balnų pavaržos, Odinės dėžutės, Piniginės iš odos, Odinės virvutės, Odinės balnų pavaržos, Odiniai lagaminai, Odinės virvelės; Lagaminai; Lietaus skėčiai, saulės skėčiai ir pakinktai; Lagaminai, rankinukai, piniginės ir kiti krepšiai; Visų pirmiau išvardytų prekių priedai ir dalys, priskirti šiai klasei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Āda un ādas imitācijas, no šiem materiāliem izgatavotas preces, Proti, ādas izstrādājumi, Savītas ādas siksnas, No ādas gatavotas kastes, Seglu jostas no ādas, Ādas futrāļi, Mazas somiņas (maki) no ādas, Ādas saites, Seglu jostas no ādas, Ādas ceļasomas, Ādas auklas; Ceļasomas un čemodāni; Lietussargi, saulessargi un zirglietas; Bagāžas somas un čemodāni, somas, naudas maki un citi piederumi lietu pārnēsāšanai; Iepriekš minēto preču daļas un piederumi, kas ietverti šajā klasē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġilda u imitazzjoni tal-ġilda u oġġetti magħmula minnhom, Jiġifieri oġġetti tal-ġilda, Ħajt tal-ġild, Kaxex magħmulin mill-ġilda, Ċingi tal-ġilda, Kartieri tad-dokumenti [oġġetti tal-ġilda], Portmonijiet tal-ġilda, Ċineg tal-ġild għat-tmexxija tal-klieb, Ċingi tal-ġilda, Valiġġi tal-ġilda, Lazzijiet (tal-ġilda); Bagolli [bagalji]; Umbrelel, parasols u oġġetti tas-sarraġ; Bagalji, basktijiet, kartieri u oġġetti oħra li ġġor fihom; Partijiet u aċċessorji għall-oġġetti kollha msemmija, inklużi f'din il-Klassi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Leder en kunstleder alsmede hieruit vervaardigde producten, Te weten schouderstukken van buffelleder, Lederdraden, Dozen van leder, Singelbanden van leder, Aktetassen [lederwaren], Lederen beurzen, Dierenriemen, Singelbanden van leder, Lederen koffers, Koorden van leder; Reiskoffers en koffers; Paraplu's, parasols en zadelmakerswaren; Bagage, tassen, knapzakken en andere draagtassen; Onderdelen en accessoires voor alle voornoemde goederen, voor zover begrepen in deze klasse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Skóra i imitacja skóry oraz wyroby z tych materiałów, Mianowicie artykuły skórzane, Nici ze skóry, Pudełka ze skóry, Paski skórzane [inne niż odzież], Teczki ze skóry, Portmonetki skórzane, Skórzane smycze, Paski skórzane [inne niż odzież], Walizki skórzane, Sznurówki skórzane; Kufry i walizki; Parasole, parasole przeciwsłoneczne i wyroby siodlarskie; Walizy, torby podróżne, torby, portfele i inne artykuły służące do przenoszenia; Akcesoria i części do wszystkich wyżej wymienionych towarów, ujęte w tej klasie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Couro e imitações do couro e produtos nestas matérias, Especificamente correame, Fios em couro, Caixas em couro, Cintas em couro, Pastas [produtos em couro], Bolsas de couro, Trelas em pele [couro], Cintas em couro, Malas de viagem em couro, Cordões em couro; Malas e maletas de viagem; Chapéus-de-chuva, chapéus-de-sol e selaria; Bagagens, malas, carteiras e outras bolsas de transporte; Peças e acessórios para todos os produtos atrás referidos, incluídos nesta classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Piele si imitatii de piele si articole fabricate din aceste materiale, Şi anume curele pentru echipamentul soldaţilor, Piele (Șnur de -), Cutii din piele, Chingi din piele, Documente (mape pentru -) [marochinărie], Portmonee de piele, Lese din piele, Chingi din piele, Valize de piele, Șireturi din piele; Cufere și geamantane; Umbrele, umbrele de soare şi articole de şelărie; Bagaje, pungi, portofele și alte accesorii; Piese şi accesorii pentru toate produsele menţionate anterior, cuprinse în această clasă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Koža a imitácia kože ako aj tovary z nich, Menovite kožené výrobky, Kožené nite, Kožené škatule, Kožené popruhy, Kožené púzdra, Kožené peňaženky, Kožené vôdzky, Kožené popruhy, Kožené kufre, Kožené šnúrky; Cestovné kufre; Dáždniky, slnečníky a sedlárske výrobky; Kufre, tašky, peňaženky a výrobky koženej galantérie; Príslušenstvo a časti všetkých vymenovaných tovarov, doteraz zahrnuté v tejto triede.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Usnje in imitacije usnja ter izdelki iz teh snovi, In sicer usnjeni predmeti, Usnjeni sukanec, Usnjene škatle, Usnjena jermena, Usnjeni toki, tulci, Denarnice iz usnja, Usnjeni povodci, Usnjena jermena, Usnjeni kovčki, Usnjene vrvice; Veliki potovalni kovčki in potovalne torbe; Dežniki, sončniki in sedlarski izdelki; Kovčki, potovalne torbe, denarnice in drugi podobni proizvodi; Deli in oprema za prej omenjeno blago, v kolikor so vključeni v ta razred.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Läder och läderimitation, samt varor framställda av dessa material, Nämligen lädervaror, Lädersnoddar, Askar tillverkade av läder, Gjordar av läder, Läderportföljer, Läderbörsar, Läderkoppel, Gjordar av läder, Koffertar av läder, Läderremmar; Koffertar och resväskor; Paraplyer, parasoller och sadelmakerivaror; Resgods, väskor, plånböcker och andra artiklar för bärhjälp; Delar och tillbehör till alla nämnda varor, ingående i denna klass.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Статуетки, фигурки и произведения на изкуството, както и украси и декорации от материали като дърво, восък, гипс или пластмаса, доколкото са включени в този клас; Мебели и мебелировка; Къщи и легла за животни; Необработени и частично обработени материали, доколкото са включени в този клас, не пригодени за определена цел, а именно кехлибар, части от животни, морска пяна, части от растения; Kонтейнери, и прегради и каси за тях, неметални; Стълби и преносими стъпала, неметални; Eкрани, стойки и знаци, неметални; Принадлежности и части за горепосочените стоки, включени в този клас.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Sochy, figurky, umělecká díla, jakož i ozdoby a dekorace z materiálů jako dřevo, vosk, sádra a plastická hmota, zařazené do této třídy; Nábytek a bytové zařízení; Přístřeší a pelíšky pro zvířata; Nezpracované a zčásti zpracované materiály, zařazené do této třídy, neupravené pro určitý účel, jmenovitě jantar, části zvířat, mořská pěna, části rostlin; Nádoby a uzávěry a držáky pro ně, nekovové; Žebříky a pohyblivé schody, nekovové; Vývěsní tabule, stojany a značky, nekovové; Části a příslušenství pro uvedené zboží, zařazené do této třídy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Statuer, figurer, kunstværker samt pynteartikler og dekorationer af materialer såsom træ, voks, gips og plastic, indeholdt i denne klasse; Møbler og møblering; Dyrehuse og senge til dyr; Uforarbejdede og delvist forarbejdede materialer, indeholdt i denne klasse, ikke tilpasset et bestemt formål, nemlig rav, dele af dyr, merskum, plantedele; Beholdere og lukninger og holdere dertil, ikke af metal; Stiger og mobile trapper, ikke af metal; Displays, standere og skilte, ikke af metal; Dele og tilbehør til alle førnævnte varer, indeholdt i denne klasse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Statuen, Figuren, Kunstwerke sowie Verzierungen und Dekorationen aus Materialien wie Holz, Wachs, Gips oder Kunststoff, soweit in dieser Klasse enthalten; Möbel und Einrichtungsgegenstände; Behausungen und Betten für Tiere; unverarbeitete und teilweise verarbeitete Materialien, nicht für einen bestimmten Gebrauchszweck angepasst, soweit in dieser Klasse enthalten, nämlich Bernstein, Tierteile, Meerschaum, Pflanzenteile; Behälter sowie Verschlüsse und Halter hierfür, nicht aus Metall; Leitern und mobile Treppen, nicht aus Metall; Displays, Ständer und Beschilderung, nicht aus Metall; Teile und Zubehör für alle vorgenannten Waren, soweit in dieser Klasse enthalten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αγάλματα, ειδώλια και έργα τέχνης καθώς και διακοσμητικά στοιχεία και διακοσμήσεις από υλικά, όπως ξύλο, κερί, γύψο και πλαστικό, εφόσον περιλαμβάνονται στην παρούσα κλάση· Έπιπλα και επίπλωση· Σπίτια ζώων και κρεβάτια· Ακατέργαστα και ημικατεργασμένα υλικά, περιλαμβανόμενα στην παρούσα κλάση, τα οποία δεν είναι προσαρμοσμένα για συγκεκριμένα χρήση, συγκεκριμένα ήλεκτρο, μέρη ζώων, σηπιόλιθος, μέρη φυτών· Δοχεία και πώματα και βάσεις κράτησης αυτών, όχι από μέταλλο· Σκάλες και κινητές σκάλες, όχι από μέταλλο· Πινακίδες, βάσεις και επιγραφές, μη μεταλλικές· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για το σύνολο των προαναφερόμενων ειδών, εφόσον περιλαμβάνονται στην παρούσα κλάση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Statues, figurines, works of art, ornaments and decorations made from materials including wood, wax, plaster and plastic, included in this class; Furniture and furnishings; Animal housing and beds; Unprocessed and semi-processed materials, included in this class and not adapted for any specific use, namely yellow amber, parts of animals, meerschaum, parts of plants; Containers, and closures and holders therefor, non-metallic; Ladders and movable steps, non-metallic; Displays, stands and signage, non-metallic; Parts and accessories for all the aforesaid goods, included in this class.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Estatuas, figuras, obras de arte, así como ornamentos y decoraciones de materiales como madera, cera, yeso y plástico, comprendidas en esta clase; Muebles y mobiliario; Camas y receptáculos para animales; Materiales no tratados y parcialmente tratados, comprendidos en esta clase, no adaptados para un uso determinado, en concreto ámbar, partes de animales, espuma de mar, partes de plantas; Recipientes, cierres y accesorios relativos a ellos, no metálicos; Escaleras y escaleras móviles, no metálicas; Expositores, estands y letreros, no metálicos; Partes y accesorios de todos estos productos, comprendidos en esta clase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kujud, kujukesed, taiesed ning puidust, vahast, kipsist ja plastist kaunistused, mis kuuluvad sellesse klassi; Mööbel ja sisustuskaubad; Lemmikloomamajad ja -asemed; Töötlemata ja osaliselt töödeldud materjalid, mis kuuluvad sellesse klassi, mis ei ole konkreetse kasutusotstarbe kaoks kohandatud, nimelt merevaik, loomaosad, sepioliit, taimeosad; Mahutid ja mahutite sulgurid ja hoidikud, v.a metallist; Redelid ja teisaldatavad trepid, v.a metallist; Tahvlid, stendid, infoekraanid (v.a metallist); Eelnimetatud kaupade osad ja tarvikud, mis kuuluvad sellesse klassi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Patsaat, veistokset, taideteokset sekä koristeet aineista, kuten puusta, vahasta, kipsistä ja muovista tässä luokassa; Huonekalut ja sisustusesineet; Eläinten kopit ja sängyt; Määrättyyn käyttötarkoitukseen sovittamattomat, työstämättömät ja osittain työstetyt aineet, tässä luokassa, nimittäin meripihka, eläinten osat, merenvaha, kasvien osat; Säiliöt sekä sulkimet ja pitimet niitä varten, muusta kuin metallista; Tikkaat ja siirrettävät portaat muusta kuin metallista; Näyttötaulut, telineet ja kyltit muusta kuin metallista; Kaikkien edellä mainittujen tavaroiden osat ja tarvikkeet tässä luokassa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Statues, figurines et œuvres d'art ainsi qu'ornements et décorations en matières telles que le bois, la cire, le plâtre et les matières plastiques, compris dans cette classe; Meubles et ameublement; Logements et lits pour animaux; Matériaux non traités et mi-ouvrés, compris dans cette classe, non adaptés à un usage déterminé, à savoir ambre, parties d'animaux, écume de mer, parties de plantes; Conteneurs, et fermetures et leurs supports, non métalliques; Échelles et marches mobiles, non en métal; Écrans, piédestaux et éléments de signalisation, non métalliques; Pièces et accessoires de tous les produits précités, compris dans cette classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kipovi, figure, umjetnička djela te ukrasi i dekoracije od materijala poput drva, voska, gipsa i plastike, ako su obuhvaćeni ovim razredom; Namještaj i oprema za kućanstvo; Kućice i kreveti za životinje; Obrađeni i djelomično obrađeni materijali, ako su obuhvaćeni ovim razredom, materijali koji nisu prilagođeni za određenu namjenu, uglavnom građevinski kamen, dijelovi životinja, morska stiva, dijelovi biljaka; Nemetalni spremnici, njihovi zatvarači i nosači; Nemetalne ljestve i pomične klupice; Zasloni, stalci i oznake, ne od metala; Dijelovi i oprema za sve prethodno spomenute proizvode ako su obuhvaćeni ovim razredom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szobrok, figurák, műalkotások, valamint díszítések és dekorációk olyan anyagokból, mint fa, viasz, gipsz és műanyag, amennyiben ebbe az osztályba tartoznak; Bútorok és lakberendezési tárgyak; Házak és fekhelyek állatoknak; Feldolgozatlan és részben feldolgozott anyagok, amennyiben ebbe az osztályba tartoznak, nem egy meghatározott használatra, nevezetesen borostyánkő, állati részek, tajték, növényi részek; Tárolók és ezekhez való fedők és fogantyúk, nem fémből; Létrák és mozgatható lépcsők, nem fémből; Display elemek, állványok és jelző- vagy hirdetőtáblák, nem fémből; A fent említett áruk részei és tartozékai, amennyiben ebbe az osztályba tartoznak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Statue, figure e opere d'arte nonché ornamenti e decorazioni in materiali come legno, cera, gesso e plastica, compresi in questa classe; Mobili e complementi di arredo; Casette e cucce per animali; Materiali non lavorati e parzialmente lavorati, appartenenti a questa classe, non adatti ad un uso specifico, ovvero ambra gialla, elementi animali, spuma di mare, parti di piante; Recipienti e loro tappi e contenitori, non in metallo; Scale e scale mobili, non in metallo; Schermi, espositori ed insegne, non in metallo; Parti e accessori per tutti i suddetti articoli, compresi in questa classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Statulėlės, figūrėlės ir meno dirbiniai bei papuošimai ir dekoracijos iš tokių medžiagų kaip medis, vaškas, gipsas ir plastikas, priskirtos šiai klasei; Baldai bei jų dalys ir priedai; Gyvūnų būstai ir gultai; Neapdirbtos ir iš dalies apdirbtos medžiagos, priskirtos šiai klasei, ne specialioms reikmėms pritaikytos medžiagos, būtent gintaras, gyvūnų dalys, jūros putos, augalų dalys; Ne metaliniai konteineriai ir jų uždoriai bei laikikliai; Ne metalinės kopėčios ir kilnojamieji laipteliai; Ne metalinės vitrinos, stendai ir iškabos; Visų pirmiau išvardytų prekių priedai ir dalys, priskirti šiai klasei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Statujas, figūras, mākslas darbi, kā arī rotājumi un dekorācijas no tādiem materiāliem kā koks, vasks, ģipsis un plastmasa, kas iekļauti šajā klasē; Mēbeles un telpu iekārtojuma priekšmeti; Dzīvnieku mājiņas un guļvietas; Neapstrādāti un daļēji apstrādāti materiāli, kas iekļauti šajā klasē, kas nav pielāgoti noteiktam lietošanas mērķim, proti, dzintars, dzīvnieku daļas, jūras putas, augu daļas; Trauki, kā arī to aizbāžņi un statīvi, kas nav no metāla; Pieslienamās un pārvietojamās kāpnes, kas nav no metāla; Ekrāni, stendi un virziena rādītāji, kas nav no metāla; Iepriekš minēto preču daļas un piederumi, kas ietverti šajā klasē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Statwi, figuri u xogħlijiet artistiċi, kif ukoll ornamenti u dekorazzjonijiet magħmula minn materjali bħal injam, xama', ġibs u plastik, inklużi f'din il-Klassi; Għamara u fornimenti; Akkomodazzjoni u friex għall-annimali; Materjali mhux proċessati u parzjalment proċessati, inklużi f'din il-klassi, mhux adattati għal skop ta' użu partikulari, jiġifieri ambra, partijiet ta' annimali, meerschaum, partijiet ta' pjanti; Kontenituri, u għeluq għall-kontenituri u ħowlders għalihom, mhux tal-metall; Slielem u turġien li jiċċaqalqu, mhux tal-metall; Displejs, tagħmir għaż-żamm ta' xi ħaġa u disinji grafiċi, mhux tal-metall; Partijiet u aċċessorji għall-oġġetti kollha msemmija, inklużi f'din il-Klassi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beelden, beeldjes, kunstwerken alsmede ornamenten en decoraties van materialen zoals hout, was, gips en plastic, voor zover begrepen in deze klasse; Meubelen en meubilair; Behuizing en bedden voor dieren; Onbewerkte en deels bewerkte materialen, voor zover begrepen in deze klasse, niet voor een bepaald gebruiksdoel aangepast, te weten barnsteen, dierlijke delen, meerschuim, plantendelen; Containers, en sluitingen en houders daarvoor, niet van metaal; Ladders en verplaatsbare trappen, niet van metaal; Uitstaleenheden, standers en signaleringsborden, niet van metaal; Onderdelen en accessoires voor alle voornoemde goederen, voor zover begrepen in deze klasse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Statuetki, figury, dzieła sztuki oraz ozdoby i dekoracje z materiałów, takich jak drewno, wosk, gips lub tworzywa sztuczne, ujęte w tej klasie; Meble i akcesoria meblowe wyposażenia domu; Budy, kojce i legowiska dla zwierząt domowych; Materiały nieobrobione lub częściowo obrobione, ujęte w tej klasie, nieprzeznaczone do konkretnego celu użytkowego, mianowicie bursztyn, części zwierząt, sepiolit, części roślin; Pojemniki, spinacze i uchwyty do nich, niemetalowe; Drabiny i ruchome schody, niemetalowe; Plansze, stoiska wystawowe i oznakowanie, niemetalowe; Akcesoria i części do wszystkich wyżej wymienionych towarów, ujęte w tej klasie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Estátuas, figuras e obras de arte, assim como ornamentos e decorações em materiais como madeira, cera, gesso e matérias plásticas, incluídos nesta classe; Mobiliário e móveis; Casas e camas para animais; Materiais em bruto e semiacabados, incluídos nesta classe, não adaptados a um determinado fim, especificamente âmbar, partes de animais, espuma do mar, partes de plantas; Contentores, e fechos e respetivos suportes, não metálicos; Escadas e degraus móveis, não metálicos; Expositores, suportes e sinalização, não metálicos; Peças e acessórios para todos os produtos atrás referidos, incluídos nesta classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Statui, figurine, lucrări de artă, precum şi ornamente şi decoraţiuni din materiale cum ar fi lemn, ceară, ipsos şi plastic, cuprinse în această clasă; Mobilă și mobilier; Adăposturi și paturi pentru animale; Materiale neprelucrate şi prelucrate parţial, cuprinse în această clasă, care nu sunt adaptate pentru un anumit scop, şi anume ambră, părţi de animale, spumă de mare, părţi de plante; Recipiente și dispozitive de închidere și suporturi pentru acestea, nemetalice; Scări și trepte mobile, nu din metal; Afișaje, standuri și indicatoare, nu din metal; Piese şi accesorii pentru toate produsele menţionate anterior, cuprinse în această clasă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Sochy, figúrky, umelecké diela, ako aj ozdoby a dekorácie z materiálov ako je drevo, vosk, sadra a plasty, zaradené do tejto triedy; Nábytok a nábytkové zariadenie; Obydlia a lôžka pre zvieratá; Nespracované a čiastočne spracované materiály, doteraz zahrnuté v tejto triede, neprispôsobené pre určitý účel použitia, menovite jantár, zvieracie časti, sépiolit, časti rastlín; Nekovové nádoby s uzávermi a držiakmi; Nekovové rebríky a prenosné schody; Nekovové vystavovacie vitríny, stojany a informačné tabule; Príslušenstvo a časti všetkých vymenovaných tovarov, doteraz zahrnuté v tejto triede.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kipi, figure, umetnine ter okrasi in dekoracije iz materialov, kot so les, vosek, mavec in plastika, ki so vključeni v ta razred; Pohištvo in pohištvena oprema; Bivališča in ležišča za živali; Nepredelani in delno predelani materiali, ki jih obsega ta razred, ne določenemu namenu uporabe prilagojeni materiali, in sicer jantar, deli živali, morska pena, deli rastlin; Posode, zapirala in držala zanje, nekovinsko; Nekovinske lestve in premične stopnice; Nekovinske razstavne površine, stojala in oznake; Deli in oprema za prej omenjeno blago, v kolikor so vključeni v ta razred.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Statyer, figurer, konstverk samt dekorationer och prydnader av material som trä, vax, gips och plast, ingående i denna klass; Möbler och inredning; Hus och bäddar för djur; Obearbetade och delvis bearbetade material, ingående i denna klass, ej avsedda för en viss användning, nämligen bärnsten, djurdelar, sjöskum, växtdelar; Containrar, och tillslutningar och hållare därtill, icke-metalliska; Stegar och mobila trappsteg, icke-metalliska; Skyltar, ställ och montrar, inte av metall; Delar och tillbehör till alla nämnda varor, ingående i denna klass.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>32</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бира и пивоварни продукти; Безалкохолни напитки; Минерални и газирани води.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pivo a pivovarnické výrobky; Nealkoholické nápoje; Minerální a sycené vody.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Øl og bryggeriprodukter; Ikke-alkoholholdige drikke; Mineralvand og kulsyreholdige vande.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bier und Brauereiprodukte; nichtalkoholische Getränke; Mineralwässer und kohlensäurehaltige Wässer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μπύρα και προϊόντα ζυθοποιίας· Μη αλκοολούχα ποτά· Μεταλλικά και αεριούχα νερά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Beer and brewery products; Non-alcoholic beverages; Mineral and aerated waters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cervezas y sus derivados; Bebidas no alcohólicas; Aguas minerales y gaseosas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Õlu ja pruulikojatooted; Alkoholivabad joogid; Gaseeritud ja mineraalveed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Oluet ja panimotuotteet; Alkoholittomat juomat; Kivennäis- ja hiilihappovedet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bière et produits de brasserie; Boissons sans alcool; Eaux minérales et gazeuses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pivo i pivarski proizvodi; Bezalkoholna pića; Mineralne i gazirane vode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Sörök és sörtermékek; Alkoholmentes italok; Ásvány- és szénsavas vizek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Birre e prodotti derivati; Bevande non alcoliche; Acque minerali e gassose.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Alus ir alaus produktai; Gaivieji gėrimai; Mineralinis ir gazuotas vanduo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Alus un alus darītavu produkti; Bezalkoholiskie dzērieni; Minerālūdeņi un gāzēti ūdeņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Birra u prodotti tal-birrerija; Xarbiet mhux alkoħoliċi; Ilma minerali u bil-gass.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bier en brouwerijproducten; Niet-alcoholische dranken; Mineraal en koolzuurhoudend water.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Piwo i produkty piwowarskie; Napoje bezalkoholowe; Wody mineralne i gazowane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cerveja e produtos de cervejaria; Bebidas sem álcool; Águas minerais e gasosas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bere și produse de bere; Băuturi nealcoolice; Ape minerale și gazoase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pivo a pivovarnícke produkty; Nealkoholické nápoje; Minerálne a sýtené vody.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pivo in pivovarski proizvodi; Brezalkoholne pijače; Mineralne in gazirane vode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Öl och bryggeriprodukter; Icke alkoholhaltiga drycker; Mineral- och kolsyrat vatten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рекламни, маркетингови и промоционални услуги; Услуги за търговия на дребно и услуги за търговия на едро във връзка с кожа и имитация на кожа, както и стоки от тях, А именно кожени калъфи, Кожени шнурове, Кожени кутии, Ремъци (кожени -), Кожени папки, Кожени торби, Каишки за кучета (Кожени -), Кожени каиши, Пътнически чанти от кожа и Връзки за обувки (от кожа), Пътни чанти и куфари, чадъри за дъжд, чадъри за слънце, Седларски принадлежности, Багаж, ръчни дамски чанти, портмонета кесии и чанти за носене на други неща, Части и фитинги за всички гореспоменати стоки, Бира и пивоварни продукти, Безалкохолни напитки, Минерални и газирани води, Mебели и обзавеждане, Канцеларски принадлежности, Играчки, Хранителни стоки, Глинени съдове, Хаусуеър, Информационно-технологични, аудиовизуални, мултимедиални и фотографски устройства,, Апарати, инструменти и кабели за електричество, Навигационни, ориентировъчни, проследяващи местоположението, проследяващи целта и картиращи уреди, измервателни и приспособления за измерване, броене, настройка, калибриране, разпознаване и наблюдение, както и регулатори, Апарати за научни изследвания и лаборатории, учебни апарати и симулатори; Услуги за търговия на дребно и на едро във връзка с очила, Огледала, Рамки за картини, Печатни материали.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Reklamní, marketingové a propagační služby; Maloobchodní a velkoobchodní služby s ohledem na kůži a její imitace a výrobky z těchto materiálů, Jmenovitě kožené řemeny, Kožené provázky, Kožené boxy, Kožené popruhy, Kožené desky, Kožené váčky, Vodítka, Pásky (kožené-), Kožené cestovní kufry a Kožené řemínky, Kufry a zavazadla, deštníky, slunečníky, Sedlářské výrobky, Zavazadla, tašky, kabelky a jiné předměty na nošení, Části a vybavení pro všechno výše uvedené zboží, Pivo a pivovarnické výrobky, Nealkoholické nápoje, Minerálních a perlivých vod, Nábytek a vybavení, Papírenské výrobky, Hračky, Potraviny, Nádobí, Domácí potřeby, Informačně technologické, audiovizuální, multimediální a fotografické přístroje, Přístroje, nástroje a kabely pro elektrický proud, Nástroje, zařízení a regulátory pro navigaci, orientaci, sledování polohy, sledování cíle, mapování, měření, identifikaci a kontrolu, Přístroje pro vědecký výzkum a laboratoře, vyučovací pomůcky a simulátory; Maloobchodní a velkoobchodní služby s ohledem na brýle, Zrcadla, Rámy, Tiskárenské výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Virksomhed vedrørende reklame, marketing og salgsfremstød; Engros- og detailhandel med læder og læderimitationer samt varer heraf, Nemlig remme til soldaters udrustning, Læderliner, Æsker af læder, Læderremme, Lædermapper, Læderpunge, Dyreliner af læder, Læderstropper, Rejseetuier af læder og Snørebånd af læder, Kufferter og rejsetasker, paraplyer og parasoller, Saddelmagervarer, Bagage, tasker, tegnebøger og andre genstande til transport af objekter, Dele og bestanddele af alle førnævnte varer, Øl og bryggeriprodukter, Ikke-alkoholholdige drikke, Mineralvande og kulsyreholdige vande, Møbler og møbelartikler, Papirhandlervarer, Legetøj, Næringsmidler, Lertøj, Husholdningsartikler, IT- og AV-udstyr, multimedieudstyr og fotoudstyr, Apparater, instrumenter og kabler til elektricitet, Navigations-, orienterings-, lokaliserings-, målsporings- og kortlægningsapparater, instrumenter, anordninger og regulatorer til måling, detektering og overvågning, Apparater til videnskabelig forskning og laboratoriebrug, undervisningsapparater og simulatorer; Detailhandel og engroshandel med briller, Spejle, Billedrammer, Tryksager.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung, Marketing und Verkaufsförderung; Einzel- und Großhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Leder und Lederimitation sowie Waren daraus, nämlich Lederzeug, Lederfäden, Lederboxen, Ledergurte, Ledermappen, Lederbeutel, Lederleinen, Lederriemen, Lederkoffer und Lederschnüre, Reise- und Handkoffer, Regenschirme, Sonnenschirme, Sattlerwaren, Gepäck, Taschen, Brieftaschen und andere Tragebehältnisse, Teile und Zubehör für alle vorgenannten Waren, Bier und Brauereiprodukte, nichtalkoholische Getränke, Mineralwässer und kohlensäurehaltige Wässer, Möbel und Einrichtungsgegenstände, Schreibwaren, Spielwaren, Lebensmittel, Geschirr, Heimtextilien, Informationstechnologische, audiovisuelle, multimediale und fotografische Geräte, Apparate, Instrumente und Kabel für Elektrizität, Navigations-, Orientierungs-, Standortverfolgungs-, Zielverfolgungs- und Kartierungsgeräte, Mess-, Erkennungs- und Überwachungsinstrumente, -vorrichtungen sowie -regler, Apparate für wissenschaftliche Forschung und Labor, Unterrichtsapparate und Simulatoren; Einzel- und Großhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Brillen, Spiegel, Rahmen und Druckereierzeugnisse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση, ενέργειες πώλησης (μάρκετινγκ) και υπηρεσίες προώθησης· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης σε σχέση με δέρμα και απομιμήσεις δέρματος καθώς και είδη από αυτά τα υλικά, Συγκεκριμένα δερμάτινα είδη, Δερμάτινα κορδόνια, Δερμάτινα κουτιά, Δερμάτινοι ιμάντες, Δερμάτινοι χαρτοφύλακες, Δερμάτινοι σάκοι, Λουριά, Δερμάτινα λουράκια, Δερμάτινες βαλίτσες και Δερμάτινα κορδόνια, Κιβώτια ταξιδίου και βαλίτσες, ομπρέλες, αλεξήλια, Είδη σελλοποιίας, Είδη αποσκευών, σάκοι, χαρτοφύλακες και άλλα είδη μεταφοράς αντικειμένων, Μέρη και εξαρτήματα όλων των προαναφερθέντων ειδών, μπύρα και προϊόντα ζυθοποιίας, Μη οινοπνευματώδη ποτά, Μεταλλικών και αεριούχων νερών, Επιπλα και είδη επίπλωσης, Είδη χαρτοπωλείου, Παιχνίδια, Ειδών διατροφής, Σερβίτσια, Οικιακά είδη, Συσκευές της τεχνολογίας πληροφοριών, οπτικοακουστικές, πολυμεσικές και φωτογραφικές, Συσκευές, όργανα και καλώδια ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος, Συσκευές πλοήγησης, προσανατολισμού, παρακολούθησης της θέσης, παρακολούθησης του στόχου και χαρτογράφησης, όργανα, διατάξεις καθώς και ρυθμιστές μέτρησης, αναγνώρισης και παρακολούθησης, Συσκευές για χρήση στην επιστημονική έρευνα και σε εργαστήρια, συσκευές διδασκαλίας και προσομοιωτές· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης σε σχέση με γυαλιά οράσεως, Καθρέπτες, Πλαίσια (κορνίζες), Έντυπο υλικό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising, marketing and promotional services; Retailing and wholesaling relating to leather and imitations of leather, and goods made therefrom, Namely straps for soldiers' equipment, Leather twist, Leather boxes, Bands of leather, Leather folders, Leather pouches, Leather leads, Leather straps, travelling cases of leather and leather laces, Trunks and travelling bags, umbrellas, parasols, Saddlery, Luggage, handbags, pocket wallets and other object carriers, Parts and fittings for all the aforesaid goods, Beers and brewery products, Non-alcoholic drinks, Mineral and aerated waters, furniture and furnishings, Stationery, Toys, Foodstuffs, Crockery, house ware, Information technology, audiovisual, multimedia and photographic apparatus, Apparatus, instruments and cables for electricity, Navigation, orientation, location tracking, target tracking and mapping apparatus, measuring, detecting and monitoring instruments, devices and regulators, Apparatus for scientific research and laboratory use, teaching apparatus and simulators; Retailing and wholesaling in relation to spectacles, Mirrors (looking glasses), Picture frames, Printed matter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios promocionales, de marketing y publicidad; Servicios de venta minorista y servicios de venta al por mayor de cuero e imitaciones de cuero así como de productos del mismo, En concreto artículos de cuero, Hilos de cuero, Cajas de cuero, Cinchas de cuero, Carpetas de cuero, Bolsas de cuero, Correas de cuero para animales, Correas de cuero, Maletas de cuero y Cordones de cuero, Baúles y maletas, paraguas, sombrillas, Artículos de guarnicionería, equipaje, bolsos, carteras y otros porta objetos, Partes y piezas de todos los productos mencionados, Cerveza y productos de cervecería, Bebidas sin alcohol, Aguas minerales y gaseosas, Muebles y mobiliario, Papelería, Juguetes, Productos alimentarios, Vajillas, Artículos de menaje, Equipos de tecnología de la información, audiovisuales, multimedia y fotográficos, Aparatos, instrumentos y cables para electricidad, Aparatos de navegación, orientación, seguimiento de la localización, seguimiento del objetivo y de mapeo, instrumentos, dispositivos así como reguladores de medida, de reconocimiento y de vigilancia, Aparatos para la investigación científica y laboratorio, aparatos de enseñanza y simuladores; Servicios de venta minorista y mayorista en relación con gafas, Espejos, Marcos, Material impreso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam ja turundus; Naha ja kunstnahka ning neist valmistatud toodete jae ning hulgimüügiteenused, Nimelt nahast kaubad, Nahknöörid, Nahkkarbid, Nahkrihmad, Nahkmapid, Nahkkukrud, Nahkrihmad, Nahast piitsapiud, Nahast reisikotid ja Nahkpaelad, Reisikastid ja reisikotid, vihmavarjud, päikesevarjud, Sadulsepatooted, Reisitarbed, kotid, rahakotid ja muud kandekotid, Kõikide eelnimetatud toodete osad ja tarvikud, Õlu ja pruulikojatooted, Alkoholita joogid, Mineraal- ja gaseerveed, Mööbel ja sisustus, Kirjatarbed, Mänguasjad, Toiduained, Lauanõud, Kodukaup, Infotehnoloogia-, audiovisuaal-, multimeedia- ja fotoseadmed, Elektriseadmed, -vahendid ja -kaablid, Navigeerimis-, orienteerumis-, asukohajälgimis-, sihtmärgijälgimis- ja kaardistamisseadmed, mõõte-, tuvastus- ja järelevalveseadmed, -vahendid ning -regulaatorid, Teaduslike uuringute ja laborite aparatuur, õppeseadmed ja simulaatorid; Jae- ja hulgimüügiteenused seoses prillidega, Peeglid, Raamid, Trükised.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta-, markkinointi- ja myynninedistämispalvelut; Nahkaan ja nahan jäljitelmiin ja niistä tehtyihin tavaroihin liittyvät vähittäis- ja tukkumyyntipalvelut, Nimittäin nahkatavarat, Nahkanyörit, Nahkalaatikot, Nahkanauhat, Nahkakansiot, Nahkapussit, Nahkataluttimet, Nahkalenkit, Nahkaiset matkalaukut ja Nahkanauhat, Matka-arkut ja -laukut, sateenvarjot, päivänvarjot, Satulavarusteet, Matkalaukkutavarat, laukut, lompakot ja muut esineiden kantovälineet, Edellä mainittujen tuotteiden osat ja varusteet, Olut ja panimotuotteet, Alkoholittomat juomat, Kivennäis- ja hiilihappovedet, Huonekalut ja kalusteet, Paperikauppatavarat, Lelut, Elintarvikkeet, Astiat, Taloustavarat, Tietotekniset, audiovisuaaliset, multimedia- ja valokuvauslaitteet, Laitteet, välineet ja kaapelit sähköä varten, Navigointi-, suunnistus-, sijainninseuranta-, kohteenseuranta- ja kartoituslaitteet, mittaus-, tunnistus- ja valvontakojeet, -laitteet sekä -säätimet, Tieteelliset tutkimus- ja laboratoriolaitteet, opetuslaitteet ja simulaattorit; Vähittäis- ja tukkumyyntipalvelut silmälasien alalla, Peilit, Kehykset, Painantaan liittyvät tuotteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de publicité, de marketing et de promotion; Services de vente au détail et en gros concernant le cuir et les imitations du cuir et les produits en ces matières, À savoir articles de maroquinerie, Lanières en cuir, Boîtes en cuir, Sangles de cuir, Serviettes en cuir, Pochettes en cuir, Laisses, Tirants (de chaussures) en cuir, Valises en cuir et Cordons en cuir, Malles et valises, parapluies, parasols, Sellerie (articles de -), Bagages, porte-monnaie, portefeuilles et autres porte-objets, Pièces et raccords pour toutes les marchandises précitées, Bières et produits de brasserie, Boissons non alcooliques, Eaux minérales et gazeuses, Meubles et ameublement, Objets de bureau, Jouets, D'articles d'alimentation, Plats, Articles de ménage, Dispositifs de la technologie de l'information, audiovisuels, multimédias et photographiques, Appareils, instruments et câbles pour l'électricité, Appareils de navigation, d'orientation, de suivi de positions, de suivi de cibles et de cartographie, instruments, dispositifs et régulateurs de mesure, de reconnaissance et de surveillance, Appareils pour la recherche scientifique et de laboratoire, appareils d'enseignement et simulateurs; Services de vente au détail et en gros en relation avec les lunettes, Glaces (miroirs), Cadres, Produits de l'imprimerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge oglašavanja, marketinga i promidžbe; Usluge maloprodaje i veleprodaje u vezi s kožom i imitacijama kože te proizvodima od navedenih materijala, I to predmeta od kože, Kožni konopci, Kožnate kutije, Uprte od kože, Kožne mape, Kožne vrećice, Kožne vodilice, Kožne vrpce, Putne torbe od kože i Kožne vezice, Putni i ručni kovčezi, kišobrani, suncobrani, Sedlarski proizvodi, Putna prtljaga, torbe, lisnice i drugi predmeti za nošenje, Dijelovi i oprema za sve gore navedene proizvode, Pivo i proizvodi za proizvodnju piva, Bezalkoholna pića koja sadrže voće, Mineralne i gazirane vode, Namještaj i oprema za kućanstvo, Papirnatih proizvoda,, Igračke, Začini, Stolno posuđe, Tekstilna roba za kućanstvo, Uređaji informacijske tehnologije, audiovizualni, multimedijski i fotografski uređaji, Aparati, instrumenti i kabeli za struju, Uređaji za navigaciju, orijentiranje, praćenje lokacije, praćenje cilja i mapiranje, mjerni, za prepoznavanje i nadzorni instrumenti, naprave te regulatori, Aparati za medicinska ispitivanja i laboratorij, nastavni aparati i simulatori; Maloprodajne i veleprodajne usluge u vezi s naočalama, Ogledala, Okviri, Tiskarski proizvodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Reklámozási, marketing és promóciós szolgáltatások; Kis- és nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások a következőkre vonatkozóan: bőr és bőrutánzatok, valamint ezekből készült áruk, Nevezetesen bőrből készült dolgok, Bőrzsinórok, Bőrdobozok, Borhevederek, Bőrmappák, Bőr erszények, Pórázok bőrből, Bőrszíjak, Bőr utazóbőröndök és Bőr zsinórok/cipőfűzők, Utazótáskák és bőröndök, esernyők, napernyők, Lószerszámok, Poggyászok, erszények, pénztárcák és egyéb tárgyakhoz való tartók, Az összes fent említett termékek alkatrészei és felszerelései, Sörök és sörtermékek, Alkoholmentes italok, Ásványvizek és dúsított vizek, Bútorok és berendezési tárgyak, Papíráruk, Játékszerek, Élelmiszerek, Edények, Háztartási cikkek, Információtechnológiai, audiovizuális, multimédiás és fényképészeti készülékek, Berendezések, műszerek és kábelek elektromossághoz, Navigációs, helymeghatározó, helykövető, célmeghatározó és feltérképező eszközök, mérő-, felismerő és felügyeleti műszerek, berendezések, valamint szabályozók, Készülékek tudományos kutatáshoz és laboratóriumokba, oktatókészülékek és szimulátorok; Kis- és nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások szemüvegek vonatkozásában, Tükrök, Képkeretek, Nyomdaipari termékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi pubblicitari, di marketing e promozionali; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e servizi di vendita all'ingrosso in relazione a cuoio e similpelle e prodotti in questo materiale, Ovvero articoli di pelle, Cordoni (in cuoio), Scatole di cuoio, Cinghie di cuoio, Cartelle di cuoio, Borsellini in pelle, Guinzagli [in pelle], Cinghie in cuoio, Valigie in cuoio e Cordoni in cuoio, Bauli e valigie, ombrelli, ombrelloni, Articoli di selleria, Bagagli, borsette, portamonete e altri portaoggetti, Parti ed accessori per tutti i suddetti prodotti, Birra e prodotti per birrifici, Bevande analcoliche, Acque minerali e gassate, Mobili e arredi, Cartoleria, Giocattoli, Prodotti alimentari, Vasellame, Articoli per la casa, Dispositivi di tecnologia dell'informazione, audiovisivi, multimediali e fotografici, Apparecchi, strumenti e cavi elettrici, Apparecchi di navigazione, orientamento, determinazione della posizione, tracciamento degli obiettivi e per la realizzazione di carte geografiche, strumenti, dispositivi e regolatori di misurazione, riconoscimento e monitoraggio, Apparecchi per la ricerca scientifica e apparecchi da laboratorio, apparecchi d'insegnamento e simulatori; Commercio al dettaglio e servizi di vendita all'ingrosso in materia d'occhiali, Specchi, Cornici, Stampati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklamos, rinkodaros ir pardavimų skatinimo paslaugos; Mažmeninės ir didmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios su odomis ir odų pakaitalais bei jų gaminiais, Būtent odiniai daiktai, Odinės virvės, Odinės dėžutės, Odinės juostos, Odiniai aplankai, Odiniai krepšeliai, Odiniai pasaitai, Diržai (odiniai --- ), Odiniai kelioniniai dėklai ir Oda ir odos atraižos, Lagaminai ir kelioniniai krepšiai, skėčiai, skėčiai nuo saulės, Pakinktai, Bagažas, rankinės, piniginės ir kiti nešiojamieji objektai, Dalys ir priedai, skirti visoms anksčiau paminėtoms prekėms, Alus ir alaus produktai, Gaivieji gėrimai, Mineralinis ir gazuotas vanduo, Baldai ir įranga, Raštinės prekės, Žaislai, Maisto prekių, Indai, Namų apyvokos reikmenys, Informacinių technologijų, garso ir vaizdo, daugialypės terpės ir fotografijos įrenginiai, Elektros aparatai, instrumentai ir kabeliai, Navigacijos, orientavimosi, buvimo vietos sekimo, tikslo sekimo ir žemėlapių sudarymo prietaisai, matavimo, atpažinimo ir stebėjimo instrumentai, įtaisai bei reguliatoriai, Mokslinių tyrimų ir laboratorijų aparatai, mokymo aparatai ir imitatoriai; Mažmeninės ir didmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios su akiniais, Veidrodžiai, Paveikslų rėmai, Spaudiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāmas, tirgvedības un preču noieta veicināšanas pakalpojumi; Mazumtirdzniecības un vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar ādu un ādas imitāciju, kā arī preces no šiem materiāliem, Proti, ādas izstrādājumi, Ādas auklas, Ādas kastes, Pletnes, Ādas mapes, Ādas maki, Ādas saites, Ādas siksnas, Ceļojumu somas no ādas un Ādas saites, Čemodāni un ceļasomas, lietussargi, saulessargi, Zirglietas, Bagāža, rokassomas, skolēnu somas un citi priekšmetu pārnēsāšanas līdzekļi, Visām iepriekšminēto preču daļas un piederumi, Alus un alus darītavu produkti, Bezalkoholiski dzērieni, bezalkoholiskie dzērieni, Minerālūdeņu un gāzētu ūdeņu, Mēbeles un to daļas, Kancelejas preces, Rotaļlietas, Pārtikas preces, Trauki, Mājsaimniecības izstrādājumi, Informācijas tehnoloģijas, audiovizuālas, multivides un fotogrāfiskas ierīces, Darbībai ar elektrību paredzētas ierīces, instrumenti un kabeļi, Navigācijas, orientēšanās, atrašanās vietas izsekošanas, mērķa izsekošanas un kartēšanas ierīces, mērīšanas, atpazīšanas un uzraudzības instrumenti, ietaises, kā arī regulatori, Zinātniskajiem pētījumiem un laboratorijām paredzēti aparāti, mācību aparāti un simulatori; Mazumtirdzniecības un vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar brillēm, Spoguļi, Rāmji, Iespiedmateriāli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' reklamar, kummerċjaliżżazzjoni u promozzjonali; Bejgħ bl-imnut u bl-ingrossa b'rabta mal-ġilda u imitazzjonijiet tal-ġilda, kif ukoll oġġetti magħmula minnhom, Jiġifieri oġġetti tal-ġilda, Ħajt tal-ġild, Kaxxi magħmula mill-ġilda, Ċineg tal-ġild għall-magni, Kartieri tal-ġilda, Boroż li jingħalqu tal-ġilda, Ċineg tal-ġild, Strixex tal-ġilda, Kaxxetti tal-ivvjaġġar tal-ġilda u Lazzijiet tal-ġilda, Bagolli u bagalji, umbrelel, parasols, Oġġetti magħmulin minn sarrâg, Bagalji, handbags, kartieri u carriers oħra, Partijiet u fittings għall-oġġetti kollha msemmija qabel, Birra u prodotti ta' birreriji, Xarbiet mhux alkoħoliċi, xorb mhux alkoħoliku, Melħ għall-ilma minerali u fexfiexi, Għamara, Kartoleriji, Ġugarelli, Oġġetti tal-ikel, Oġġett tax-xaqquf, Oġġetti tad-dar, Tagħmir tat-teknoloġija tal-informatika, awdjoviżiva, multimedjali u fotografika, Apparat, strumenti u kejbils għall-elettriċità, Tagħmir tar-regolazzjoni għan-navigazzjoni, orjentazzjoni, rintraċċar, insegwiment tal-bersall u mmappjar, strumenti, tagħmir, kif ukoll regolaturi tal-kejl, identifikazzjoni u monitoraġġ, Apparat għar-riċerka xjentifika u l-laboratorju, apparat tat-tagħlim u simulaturi; Servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut u bl-ingrossa b'rabta ma' nuċċalijiet, Mirja, Frejmijiet ta' l-istampi, Materjal stampat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reclame, marketing en promotionele diensten; Detail- en groothandel in leder en kunstleder en hieruit vervaardigde producten, Namelijk schouderstukken van buffelleder, Koorden van leder, Lederen boxen, Singelband van leder, Mappen van leder, Lederen zakjes, Dierenriemen, Riemen van leder, Koffers van leder en Koorden van leder, Reiskoffers en koffers, paraplu's, parasols, Zadelmakerswaren, Bagage, tassen, aktetassen en andere draagmiddelen, Onderdelen en hulpstukken voor alle bovengenoemde waren, Bier- en brouwerijproducten, Alcoholvrije dranken, Mineraalwater en koolzuurhoudend water, Meubelen en meubilering, Schrijfwaren, Speelgoed, Voedingsmiddelen, Vaatwerk, Huishoudelijke artikelen, Informatietechnologische, audiovisuele, multimediale en fotografische toestellen, Apparaten, instrumenten en kabels voor elektriciteit, Apparaten voor het navigeren, gidsen, volgen, plaats bepalen en het maken van kaarten, instrumenten voor het meten, detecteren en bewaken, indicatoren en controle-instrumenten, Apparaten voor wetenschappelijk onderzoek en laboratoria, onderwijstoestellen en simulatoren; Detail- en groothandelsdiensten met betrekking tot brillen, Spiegels, Kozijnen, Drukwerken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi reklamowe, marketingowe i promocyjne; Usługi w zakresie sprzedaży detalicznej i hurtowej skór i imitacji skór oraz wyrobów z nich wykonanych, Mianowicie artykuły skórzane, skórzane sznury, Pojemniki skórzane, Paski skórzane, Foldery skórzane, Torebki skórzane, Skórzane smycze, Skórzane paski, Etui podróżne ze skóry i Skórzane (smycze -), Kufry i walizki, parasole, parasole przeciwsłoneczne, Wyroby siodlarskie, Bagaż, torby, tornistry i inne produkty do przenoszenia rzeczy, Części i akcesoria do wszystkich wyżej wymienionych towarów, Piwo i produkty piwowarskie, Napoje bezalkoholowe, wód mineralnych i gazowanych, Meble i wyposażenie, Artykuły papiernicze, Zabawki, Artykuły spożywcze, Naczynia stołowe, Odziez domowa, Urządzenia informatyczne, audiowizualne, multimedialne i fotograficzne, Przyrządy, urządzenia i kable elektryczne, Przyrządy, urządzenia i regulatory nawigacyjne, orientacyjne, lokalizacyjne, śledzące i mapujące, przyrządy, urządzenia i regulatory pomiarowe, rozpoznawcze i nadzorcze, Urządzenia do badań naukowych i do laboratorium, urządzenia dydaktyczne i symulatory; Usługi handlu detalicznego i hurtowego w zakresie okularów, Lustra, Ramy do obrazów, Druki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de publicidade, de marketing e de promoção; Serviços de comércio retalhista e grossista relacionados com couros e imitações de couro e produtos nestas matérias, Especificamente correame, Fios de couro, Caixas em couro, Correias de couro, Pastas em couro, Bolsas de couro, Trelas, Tiras de couro, Malas em couro e Cordões em couro, Malas e maletas de viagem, chapéus-de-chuva, chapéus-de-sol, Artigos de selaria, Artigos de bagagem, malas, carteiras e outros porta objetos, Peças e componentes de todos os artigos atrás referidos, Cerveja e produtos de cervejaria, Bebidas não alcoólicas, Águas minerais e com gás, Móveis e guarnições, Artigos de papelaria, Brinquedos, Produtos alimentares, Pratos, Artigos para a casa, Aparelhos de tecnologias da informação, audiovisuais, multimédia e fotográficos, Aparelhos, instrumentos e cabos para sistemas elétricos, Aparelhos de navegação, orientação, localização, seguimento e cartografia, instrumentos, dispositivos e reguladores de medida, deteção e monitorização, Aparelhos para a investigação científica e laboratório, aparelhos de ensino e simuladores; Serviços de comércio retalhista e grossista de óculos, Espelhos, Molduras, Material impresso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de publicitate, marketing și promovare; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul și cu ridicata în legătură cu piele și imitații de piele, produse din aceste materiale, Și anume articole din piele, Şnururi din piele, Cutii din piele, Curele din piele, Mape din piele, Pungi din piele, Lese, Curele din piele, Genți de voiaj din piele şi Şireturi (piele), Cufere si genti de voiaj, umbrele de ploaie, umbrele de soare, Articole de şelărie, Bagaje, poșete, ghiozdane și alte genți port-obiecte, Piese si racorduri pentru toate bunurile mentionate anterior, Bere şi produse din industria berii, Băuturi nealcoolice, Ape minerale şi carbogazoase, Mobile şi mobilier, Articole de papetarie, Jucării, Produse alimentare, Veselă, Articole pentru casă, Aparate de tehnologia informaţiei, audiovizuale, multimedia şi de fotografiat, Aparate, instrumente şi cabluri pentru electricitate, Instrumente, dispozitive, precum și regulatoare de navigație, de orientare, de urmărire, de localizare a țintei și de cartografiere, de măsurare, de recunoaștere și de monitorizare, Aparate de cercetare ştiinţifică şi laborator, aparate didactice şi simulatoare; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul şi cu ridicata în legătură cu ochelari, Oglinzi, Rame de fotografie, Produse de imprimerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklamné, marketingové a propagačné služby; Maloobchodné a veľkoobchodné služby so zameraním na kožu a koženku, ako aj tovary z nich, Menovite kožené výrobky, Kožené šnúry, Kožené boxy, Remienky (kožené -), Kožené šanóny a krúžkové zaraďovače (kancelárske potreby), Kožené vrecká, Kožené vôdzky, Kožené remienky, Kožené cestovné puzdrá a Kožené šnúrky, Lodné kufre a kufre, dáždniky, slnečníky, Sedlárske výrobky, Kufre, tašky, peňaženky a výrobky koženej galantérie, Časti a súčasti pre všetky vyššie uvedené tovary, Pivo a pivovarnícke výrobky, Nealkoholické nápoje, Minerálnych a sýtených vôd, Nábytok a zariadenia, Papiernický tovar, Hračky, Potravinárskeho tovaru, Riad, Náčinie do domácnosti, Informačné technológie, zvukovo-obrazové, multimediálne a fotografické prístroje, Aparáty, nástroje a káble pre elektrinu, Navigačné, orientačné prístroje, prístroje na sledovanie aktuálnej polohy, prístroje na sledovanie cieľa a mapovacie prístroje, meracie, rozpoznávacie a monitorovacie nástroje, zariadenia, ako aj regulátory, Aparáty na vedecký výskum a laboratóriá, vyučovacie prístroje a simulátory; Maloobchodný a veľkoobchodný predaj so zameraním na okuliare, Zrkadlá, Rámy na obrazy, Tlačoviny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglaševalske, tržne in promocijske storitve; Maloprodajne in veleprodajne storitve v zvezi z usnjem in imitacijami usnja ter izdelki iz teh snovi, In sicer usnjeni predmeti, Usnjene vrvice, Usnjene škatle, Jermeni iz usnja, Usnjene mape, Usnjeni mošnjički, Usnjene povezke (opasači), Usnjeni trakovi, Potovalne torbice iz usnja in Usnjeni trakovi, Veliki potovalni kovčki in ročni kovčki, dežniki, sončniki, Sedlarski izdelki, Prtljaga, torbe, aktovke in druge torbe za predmete, Deli in dodatki za vse prej omenjeno blago, Pivo in pivovarski izdelki, Nealkoholne pijače, Mineralne in gazirane vode, Pohištvo in oprema, Pisarniški material, Igrače, Živila, Posoda, Gospodinjski izdelki, Informacijsko-tehnološke, avdiovizualne, multimedijske in fotografske naprave, Aparati, instrumenti in kabli za elektriko, Naprave za navigacijo, orientacijo, sledenje lokacijam, sledenje ciljem in kartiranje, merilni, identifikacijski in nadzorni instrumenti, priprave ter regulatorji, Aparati za znanstvene raziskave in laboratorije, naprave za učenje in simulatorji; Maloprodajne in veleprodajne storitve v zvezi z očali, Ogledala (zrcala), Okviri, Tiskarski izdelki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reklam, marknadsföring och säljfrämjande tjänster; Detalj- och grosshandelstjänster med avseende på läder och läderimitationer samt varor därav, Nämligen lädervaror, Lädersnören, Läderlådor, Läderband, Lädermappar, Läderpåsar, Läderkoppel, Läderstroppar, Resväskor av läder och Läderskosnören, Koffertar och resväskor, paraplyer, parasoller, Sadelmakerivaror, Resväskor, handväskor, portföljer och andra bärväskor, Delar och komponenter till alla nämnda varor, Öl och bryggeriprodukter, Icke alkoholhaltiga drycker, Mineralvatten och sodavatten, Möbler och inredningsartiklar, Pappersvaror, Leksaker, Livsmedel, Kärl, Hushållsvaror, Informationstekniska, audiovisuella, multimediala och fotografiska anordningar, Apparater, instrument och kablar för elektricitet, Navigerings-, orienterings-, lokaliserings-, målspårnings- och kartläggningsanordningar, mät-, identifierings- och övervakningsinstrument, -anordningar samt -regulatorer, Apparater för vetenskaplig forskning och laboratorier, apparater för undervisning och simulatorer; Detalj- och grosshandelstjänster med avseende på glasögon, Speglar, Tavelramar, Tryckmaterial.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/158</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1060234</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>12171</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
