<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-18T02:29:03</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018340096</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018340096</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-11-18</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>es</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="1" status="1">Application filed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-11-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>MB Premium Gloves</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Найлонови ръкавици за еднократна употреба за лаборатории; Латексови ръкавици за еднократна употреба за лаборатории; Ръкавици за водолази; Огнеупорни ръкавици.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Jednorázové plastové rukavice pro laboratorní použití; Latexové rukavice pro laboratorní účely na jedno použití; Potápěčské rukavice; Ohnivzdorné rukavice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Engangshandsker af plastik til laboratoriebrug; Engangshandsker af latex til laboratoriebrug; Dykkerhandsker; Brandsikre handsker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wegwerfbare Kunststoffhandschuhe für den Laborgebrauch; Wegwerfbare Latexhandschuhe für den Laborgebrauch; Taucherhandschuhe; Feuerfeste Handschuhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πλαστικά γάντια μίας χρήσης για εργαστηριακούς σκοπούς· Γάντια μιας χρήσης από λατέξ για εργαστηριακούς σκοπούς· Γάντια κατάδυσης· Πυράντοχα γάντια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Disposable plastic gloves for laboratory use; Disposable latex gloves for laboratory use; Gloves for divers; Fire resistant gloves.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Guantes de plástico desechables para laboratorios; Guantes de látex desechables para laboratorios; Guantes de buceo; Guantes resistentes al fuego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ühekordsed plastkindad laborikasutuseks; Ühekordsed latekskindad laborikasutuseks; Kindad sukeldujatele; Tulekindlad kindad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kertakäyttöiset muovikäsineet laboratoriokäyttöön; Kertakäyttöiset lateksikäsineet laboratoriokäyttöön; Käsineet (Sukellus -); Tulenkestävät käsineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Gants jetables en plastique de laboratoire; Gants jetables en latex de laboratoire; Gants de plongée; Gants ignifuges.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Jednokratne plastične rukavice za laboratorije; Jednokratne rukavice od lateksa za laboratorijsku uporabu; Rukavice za ronioce; Rukavice otporne na vatru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Eldobható műanyag kesztyűk laboratóriumi használatra; Eldobható latex kesztyűk laboratóriumi használatra; Búvárkesztyűk; Tűzálló kesztyűk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Guanti di plastica monouso per laboratorio; Guanti di lattice monouso per laboratorio; Guanti per subacquei; Guanti ignifughi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vienkartinės laboratorinės plastikinės pirštinės; Vienkartinės latekso pirštinės laboratorijų reikmėms; Narų pirštinės; Ugniai atsparios pirštinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vienreizlietojami plastmasas cimdi izmantošanai laboratorijā; Vienreizlietojami lateksa cimdi izmantošanai laboratorijā; Nirēju un ūdenslīdēju cimdi; Ugunsdrošie cimdi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ingwanti tal-lastku li jintremew wara li jintużaw għall-użu fil-laboratorju; Ingwanti tal-lastiku li jintużaw darba biss għall-użu fil-laboratorju; Ingwanti għall-għaddasa; Ingwanti reżistenti għan-nar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Plastic wegwerphandschoenen voor laboratoriumgebruik; Latex wegwerphandschoenen voor laboratoriumgebruik; Duikerhandschoenen; Brandwerende handschoenen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Jednorazowe rękawiczki z tworzyw sztucznych do użytku laboratoryjnego; Jednorazowe rękawiczki lateksowe do użytku laboratoryjnego; Rękawice dla nurków; Rękawice ogniotrwałe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Luvas de plástico descartáveis para uso em laboratório; Luvas de látex descartáveis para uso em laboratório; Luvas para mergulho; Luvas resistentes ao fogo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mănuși de plastic de unică folosință pentru laborator; Mănuși de latex de unică folosință pentru laborator; Mănuși de scafandru; Mănuși rezistente la foc.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Jednorazové plastové rukavice na laboratórne účely; Jednorazové latexové rukavice na laboratórne účely; Potápačské rukavice; Ohňovzdorné rukavice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Rokavice iz plastike za enkratno uporabo, za laboratorijsko uporabo; Rokavice iz lateksa za enkratno uporabo, za laboratorijsko uporabo; Rokavice za potapljače; Ognjevzdržne rokavice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Plasthandskar av engångstyp för laboratorieanvändning; Latexhandskar av engångstyp för laboratorieanvändning; Handskar för dykare; Brandsäkra handskar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицински ластични дрехи; Латексови ръкавици за медицински преглед; Латексови ръкавици за медицинска употреба; Гумени ръкавици за медицинска употреба; Латексови ръкавици за стоматологични цели; Латексови ръкавици за хирургическа употреба; Латексови ръкавици за ветеринарни цели; Гумени ръкавици за хирургична употреба; Защитни ръкавици за еднократна употреба, за медицински цели; Защитни ръкавици за медицински цели; Предпазни ръкавици за ветеринарни цели; Ръкавици за еднократна употреба за хирургични цели; Ръкавици за еднократна употреба за ветеринарни цели; Медицински ръкавици за прегледи; Ръкавици за употреба по време на операции; Ръкавици за употреба в болнична среда; Ръкавици за стоматологични цели; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Ръкавици за ветеринарни цели; Защитни ръкавици за употреба от хирурзи по време на операции; Защитни ръкавици за хора, работещи в медицинския сектор; Защитни ръкавици за хора, работещи в стоматологичния сектор; Хирургически ръкавици; Облекло, шапки и принадлежности за глава, обувки за медицински персонал и пациенти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kompresní oděvy pro léčebnou terapii; Latexové vyšetřovací rukavice pro lékařské použití; Latexové rukavice pro lékařské účely; Gumové rukavice k lékařskému použití; Latexové rukavice pro zubní účely; Latexové rukavice pro chirurgické účely; Latexové rukavice pro veterinární účely; Gumové rukavice k chirurgickému použití; Jednorázové ochranné rukavice k lékařským účelům; Ochranné rukavice pro lékařské účely; Ochranné rukavice pro veterinární účely; Jednorázové rukavice pro chirurgické účely; Jednorázové rukavice pro veterinární účely; Rukavice pro lékařská vyšetření; Operační rukavice; Rukavice pro použití v nemocnicích; Rukavice ke stomatologickému použití; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Rukavice pro veterinární použití; Ochranné rukavice používané chirurgy během operací; Ochranné rukavice používané pracovníky ve zdravotnictví; Ochranné rukavice používané pracovníky ve stomatologii; Chirurgické rukavice; Oděvy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pro zdravotnické pracovníky a pacienty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande til anvendelse i medicinsk trykbehandling; Undersøgelseshandsker af latex til medicinske formål; Handsker af latex til medicinsk brug; Gummihandsker til medicinske formål; Latexhandsker til dentale formål; Latexhandsker til kirurgiske formål; Latexhandsker til veterinære formål; Gummihandsker til kirurgisk brug; Beskyttelseshandsker til engangsbrug til medicinske formål; Beskyttelseshandsker til medicinske formål; Beskyttelseshandsker til veterinære formål; Engangshandsker til kirurgiske formål; Engangshandsker til veterinære formål; Medicinske undersøgelseshandsker; Handsker til brug under operationer; Handsker til brug på hospitaler; Handsker til dental brug; Handsker til medicinske formål; Handsker til veterinærmedicinske formål; Beskyttelseshandsker til brug for kirurger under operationer; Beskyttelseshandsker til medicisk brug til personer, som arbejder inden for lægevirksomhed; Beskyttelseshandsker til brug for personer, der udfører tandlægearbejde; Kirurgiske handsker; Beklædningsgenstande, hovedbeklædning og fodtøj til medicinsk personale og patienter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Druckbekleidungsstücke für die medizinische Behandlung; Latexuntersuchungshandschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Latexhandschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Gummihandschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Latexhandschuhe für zahnärztliche Zwecke; Latexhandschuhe für chirurgische Zwecke; Latexhandschuhe für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Gummihandschuhe für chirurgische Zwecke; Einwegschutzhandschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Schutzhandschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Schutzhandschuhe für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Einweghandschuhe für chirurgische Zwecke; Einweghandschuhe für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Medizinische Untersuchungshandschuhe; Handschuhe zur Verwendung bei Operationen; Handschuhe zur Verwendung in Krankenhäusern; Handschuhe für zahnärztliche Zwecke; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Handschuhe für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Schutzhandschuhe für Chirurgen zur Verwendung bei Operationen; Schutzhandschuhe für medizinisches Personal; Schutzhandschuhe für zahnärztliches Personal; Operationshandschuhe; Bekleidung, Kopfbedeckungen und Schuhwaren für medizinisches Personal und Patienten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα άσκησης πίεσης για ιατρική θεραπεία· Εξεταστικά γάντια λατικού (λάτεξ) για ιατρική χρήση· Γάντια από λάτεξ για την ιατρική· Γάντια από καουτσούκ για ιατρική χρήση· Γάντια από λάτεξ για οδοντιατρική χρήση· Γάντια λατικού (λατέξ) για χειρουργική χρήση· Γάντια από λάτεξ για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Γάντια από καουτσούκ για χειρουργική χρήση· Προστατευτικά γάντια μιας χρήσης για ιατρικές χρήσεις· Προστατευτικά γάντια για ιατρική χρήση· Προστατευτικά γάντια για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Γάντια μιας χρήσης για χειρουργική χρήση· Γάντια μιας χρήσης για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Γάντια ιατρικής εξέτασης· Γάντια για χρήση σε επεμβάσεις· Γάντια για νοσοκομειακή χρήση· Γάντια για οδοντιατρική χρήση· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Γάντια για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Προστατευτικά γάντια για χρήση από χειρουργούς σε επεμβάσεις· Προστατευτικά γάντια για εργαζομένους στον τομέα της ιατρικής· Προστατευτικά γάντια για εργαζομένους στον τομέα της οδοντιατρικής· Χειρουργικά γάντια· Ενδύματα, είδη πιλοποιίας και υποδήματα για ιατρικό προσωπικό και ασθενείς..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Pressure garments for medical treatment; Latex examination gloves for medical use; Latex gloves for medical use; Rubber gloves for medical use; Latex gloves for dental use; Latex gloves for surgical use; Latex gloves for veterinary use; Rubber gloves for surgical use; Disposable protective gloves for medical purposes; Protective gloves for medical use; Protective gloves for veterinary use; Disposable gloves for surgical use; Disposable gloves for veterinary use; Gloves for medical examinations; Gloves for use during operations; Gloves for use in hospitals; Gloves for dental use; Gloves for medical purposes; Gloves for veterinary use; Protective gloves for use by surgeons during operations; Protective gloves for use by persons working in medicine; Protective gloves for use by persons working in the dentistry; Surgical gloves; Clothing, headgear and footwear for medical personnel and patients.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir de compresión para el tratamiento médico; Guantes de examen de látex para uso médico; Guantes de látex de uso médico; Guantes de látex para uso médico; Guantes de látex para uso odontológico; Guantes de látex para uso quirúrgico; Guantes de látex para uso veterinario; Guantes de látex quirúrgicos; Guantes de protección desechables para uso médico; Guantes de protección para uso médico; Guantes de protección para uso veterinario; Guantes desechables para uso quirúrgico; Guantes desechables para uso veterinario; Guantes para exámenes médicos; Guantes para su uso durante operaciones; Guantes para su uso en hospitales; Guantes para uso dental; Guantes para uso médico; Guantes para uso veterinario; Guantes protectores para su uso por cirujanos durante operaciones; Guantes protectores para su utilización por personas que trabajan en el ámbito de la medicina; Guantes protectores para su utilización por personas que trabajan en el ámbito de la odontología; Guantes quirúrgicos; Prendas de vestir, artículos de sombrerería y calzado para el personal médico y los pacientes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Surverõivad meditsiiniliste protseduuride jaoks; Latekskindad meditsiiniliseks läbivaatuseks; Latekskindad meditsiiniliseks kasutuseks; Meditsiinilised kummikindad; Hambaravis kasutatavad latekskindad; Latekskindad kirurgiliseks kasutuseks; Veterinaarsed latekskindad; Kirurgilised kummikindad; Ühekordselt kasutatavad kaitsekindad (meditsiinilised); Meditsiinilised kaitsekindad; Veterinaarias kasutatavad kaitsekindad; Ühekordsed kindad kirurgias kasutuseks; Ühekordsed kindad veterinaarias kasutamiseks; Meditsiinilise läbivaatuse kindad; Kindad kasutamiseks operatsioonide kestel; Kindad haiglates kasutamiseks; Hambaarstikindad; Meditsiinilised kindad; Veterinaarikindad; Kirurgide kaitsekindad operatsiooniks; Kaitsekindad meditsiinitöötajatele; Stomatoloogilise personali kaitsekindad; Kirurgilised kindad; Meditsiinitöötajate ja patsientide rõivad, peakatted ja jalatsid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Painevaatteet lääkinnälliseen hoitoon; Lateksikäsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Lateksikäsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Kumikäsineet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Lateksikäsineet hammaslääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Lateksikäsineet kirurgiseen käyttöön; Lateksikäsineet eläinlääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kumikäsineet kirurgiseen käyttöön; Kertakäyttöiset suojakäsineet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojakäsineet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojakäsineet eläinlääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kertakäyttökäsineet kirurgisiin tarkoituksiin; Kertakäyttökäsineet eläinlääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Käsineet lääketieteellisiin tutkimuksiin; Leikkausten aikana käytettävät käsineet; Sairaaloissa käytettävät käsineet; Käsineet hammaslääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Käsineet eläinlääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Suojakäsineet kirurgien käyttöön leikkausten aikana; Suojakäsineet lääketieteen alalla toimivien henkilöiden käyttöön; Suojakäsineet hammaslääketieteen alalla toimivien henkilöiden käyttöön; Leikkauskäsineet; Vaatteet, päähineet ja jalkineet lääkintähenkilöstölle ja potilaille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements de compression pour traitement médical; Gants d'examen en latex à usage médical; Gants en latex à usage médical; Gants en caoutchouc à usage médical; Gants en latex à usage dentaire; Gants en latex à usage chirurgical; Gants en latex à usage vétérinaire; Gants en caoutchouc à usage chirurgical; Gants de protection jetables à usage médical; Gants protecteurs à usage médical; Gants protecteurs à usage vétérinaire; Gants jetables à usage chirurgical; Gants jetables à usage vétérinaire; Gants pour examens médicaux; Gants à utiliser pendant des opérations; Gants à usage médical utilisés dans les hôpitaux; Gants à usage dentaire; Gants à usage médical; Gants à usage vétérinaire; Gants de protection destinés aux interventions chirurgicales; Gants de protection pour le personnel médical; Gants de protection pour le personnel dentaire; Gants chirurgicaux; Vêtements, articles de chapellerie et articles chaussants pour personnel médical et patients.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kompresivna odjeća za medicinsko liječenje; Liječničke rukavice od lateksa za preglede; Medicinske rukavice od lateksa; Gumene rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Rukavice od lateksa za dentalne potrebe; Rukavice od lateksa za kiruršku uporabu; Rukavice od lateksa za veterinarske svrhe; Gumene rukavice za kiruršku uporabu; Jednokratne zaštitne rukavice za medicinske svrhe; Zaštitne rukavice za medicinske svrhe; Zaštitne rukavice za veterinarske svrhe; Jednokratne rukavice za kirurške svrhe; Jednokratne rukavice za veterinarske svrhe; Rukavice za medicinske preglede; Rukavice za uporabu tijekom operacije; Rukavice za uporabu u bolnicama; Rukavice za stomatološku uporabu; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Rukavice za veterinarsku uporabu; Zaštitne rukavice za kirurge za uporabu tijekom operacija; Zaštitne rukavice za djelatnike u medicini; Zaštitne rukavice za djelatnike u stomatologiji; Kirurške rukavice; Odjeća, pokrivala za glavu i obuća za medicinsko osoblje i pacijente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nyomóruházat orvosi kezeléshez; Latex vizsgálókesztyűk orvosi használatra; Latex kesztyűk orvosi használatra; Orvosi gumikesztyűk; Fogászati latex kesztyűk; Latex kesztyűk sebészeti használatra; Latex kesztyűk állatorvosi célra; Sebészeti gumikesztyűk; Eldobható védőkesztyűk orvosi használatra; Védőkesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Védőkesztyűk állatorvosi célra; Eldobható kesztyűk sebészeti célra; Eldobható kesztyűk állatorvosi célra; Orvosi vizsgálókesztyűk; Operációk során használatos kesztyűk; Kórházban használatos kesztyűk; Fogászati kesztyűk; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Állatorvosi kesztyűk; Műtétekhez használt védőkesztyűk sebészek számára; Védőkesztyűk egészségügyi [orvosi] személyzet számára; Védőkesztyűk fogászati személyzet számára; Sebészeti kesztyűk; Ruházat, fejfedők és lábbelik ápolószemélyzet és páciensek számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Indumenti a compressione per trattamenti medici; Guanti da esame in lattice per uso medico; Guanti in lattice per uso medico; Guanti di gomma per uso medico; Guanti di lattice per uso odontoiatrico; Guanti in lattice per uso chirurgico; Guanti di lattice per uso veterinario; Guanti di gomma per uso chirurgico; Guanti protettivi usa e getta per uso medico; Guanti di protezione per uso medico; Guanti di protezione per uso veterinario; Guanti monouso per uso chirurgico; Guanti monouso per uso veterinario; Guanti per esami medici; Guanti per utilizzo durante operazioni; Guanti per ospedali; Guanti per uso dentistico; Guanti per uso medico; Guanti per uso veterinario; Guanti di protezione per chirurghi, per uso durante operazioni; Guanti protettivi per personale medico; Guanti protettivi per personale odontoiatrico; Guanti chirurgici; Capi d'abbigliamento, articoli di cappelleria e calzature per personale medico e pazienti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Spaudžiantys (kompresiniai) drabužiai medicininio gydymo reikmėms; Lateksinės apžiūros pirštinės medicinos reikmėms; Latekso pirštinės medicinos reikmėms; Guminės pirštinės medicinos reikmėms; Latekso pirštinės odontologijos reikmėms; Latekso pirštinės chirurgijos reikmėms; Latekso pirštinės veterinarijos reikmėms; Chirurginės guminės pirštinės; Vienkartinės apsauginės pirštinės medicinos reikmėms; Apsauginės pirštinės medicinos reikmėms; Apsauginės pirštinės veterinarijos reikmėms; Vienkartinės pirštinės chirurgijos reikmėms; Vienkartinės pirštinės veterinarijos reikmėms; Medicininės apžiūros pirštinės; Operacinės pirštinės; Pirštinės, skirtos naudoti ligoninėse; Odontologinės pirštinės; Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Veterinarinės pirštinės; Apsauginės chirurginės pirštinės, skirtos naudoti operacijų metu; Medicinos personalo apsauginės pirštinės; Odontologų apsauginės pirštinės; Chirurginės pirštinės; Apranga, galvos apdangalai ir avalynė medicinos personalui ir pacientams.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbs ar spiediena efektu terapeitiskai ārstēšanai; Izmeklējumu cimdi no lateksa medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Lateksa medicīniskie cimdi; Gumijas cimdi medicīniskam nolūkam; Lateksa cimdi zobārstniecības nolūkiem; Lateksa cimdi ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Lateksa cimdi veterinārijas nolūkiem; Gumijas cimdi, kas paredzēti lietošanai ķirurģijā; Vienreizlietojami aizsargcimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Aizsargcimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Aizsargcimdi izmantošanai veterinārijā; Vienreizlietojami cimdi ķirurģijas nolūkiem; Vienreizlietojami cimdi veterinārijas nolūkiem; Medicīniskās apskates cimdi; Cimdi, kurus izmanto operācijām; Cimdi, kurus izmanto slimnīcā; Cimdi, kas paredzēti izmantošanai zobārstniecībā; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Cimdi, kas paredzēti izmantošanai veterinārijā; Operāciju aizsargcimdi ķirurgiem; Aizsargcimdi medicīnas nozarē strādājošām personām; Aizsargcimdi zobārstniecības nozarē strādājošām personām; Ķirurģiskie cimdi; Apģērbi, galvassegas un apavi medicīnas personālam un pacientiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħwejjeġ tal-pressjoni għal trattament mediku; Ingwanti tal-eżaminazzjoni magħmula mil-gommalastika għall-użu mediku; Ingwanti tal-gommalastika għal użu mediku; Ingwanti tal-lastku għall-użu mediku; Ingwanti lattiċi għal skopijiet dentali; Ingwanti tal-gommalastika għall-użu kirurġiku; Ingwanti lattiċi għal skopijiet veterinarji; Ingwanti tal-lastku għall-użu kirurġiku; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi li jistgħu jintremew; Ingwanti protettivi għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti protettivi għal skopijiet veterinarji; Ingwanti għal skopijiet kirurġiċi li jintremew wara l-użu; Ingwanti għal skopijiet veterinarji li jintremew wara l-użu; Ingwanti għall-eżaminazzjonijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għall-użu waqt l-operazzjonijiet; Ingwanti għal użu fi sptarijiet; Ingwanti għall-użu dentali; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għall-użu veterinarju; Ingwanti protettivi għall-użu minn kirurgi waqt l-operazzjonijiet; Ingwanti protettivi għall-użu minn persuni li jaħdmu fil-mediċina; Ingwanti protettivi għall-użu minn persuni li jaħdmu fid-dentistrija; Ingwanti tal-kirurġija; Ħwejjeġ, xedd ir-ras u xedd is-saqajn għall-persunal fil-qasam mediku u għall-pazjenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Drukkleding voor medische behandeling; Latex onderzoekshandschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Handschoenen van latex voor medisch gebruik; Rubberen handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Latexhandschoenen voor tandheelkundige doeleinden; Latexhandschoenen voor chirurgisch gebruik; Latexhandschoenen voor diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Rubberen handschoenen voor chirurgisch gebruik; Wegwerp beschermende handschoenen voor medische doeleinden; Beschermende handschoenen voor medische doeleinden; Beschermende handschoenen voor diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Wegwerphandschoenen voor chirurgische doeleinden; Wegwerphandschoenen voor diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Handschoenen voor medisch onderzoek; Handschoenen voor gebruik tijdens operaties; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik in ziekenhuizen; Handschoenen voor tandheelkundig gebruik; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Handschoenen voor diergeneeskundig gebruik; Beschermende handschoenen voor gebruik door chirurgen tijdens operaties; Beschermende handschoenen voor gebruik door personen die werkzaam zijn in de medische sector; Beschermende handschoenen voor gebruik door personen die werkzaam zijn in de tandheelkundige sector; Chirurgische handschoenen; Kleding, hoofdbedekking en schoeisel voor medisch personeel en patiënten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież uciskowa do terapii medycznych; Lateksowe rękawice do badania do użytku medycznego; Rękawice lateksowe do celów medycznych; Rękawice gumowe do użytku medycznego; Rękawiczki lateksowe do celów stomatologicznych; Lateksowe rękawiczki do użytku chirurgicznego; Rękawiczki lateksowe do celów weterynaryjnych; Rękawice gumowe do użytku chirurgicznego; Jednorazowe rękawice ochronne do celów medycznych; Rękawiczki ochronne do celów medycznych; Rękawiczki ochronne do celów weterynaryjnych; Jednorazowe rękawiczki do celów chirurgicznych; Jednorazowe rękawiczki do celów weterynaryjnych; Rękawice do badań medycznych; Rękawice do użytku podczas operacji; Rękawice do użytku w szpitalach; Rękawice do użytku stomatologicznego; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Rękawice do użytku weterynaryjnego; Rękawice ochronne do użytku przez chirurgów podczas operacji; Rękawice ochronne do stosowania przez pracowników medycznych; Rękawice ochronne do użytku przez pracowników stomatologii; Rękawice chirurgiczne; Odzież, nakrycia głowy i obuwie dla personelu medycznego i pacjentów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário de compressão para tratamento médico; Luvas de examinação de látex para uso médico; Luvas de látex para uso médico; Luvas de borracha para uso médico; Luvas de látex para uso odontológico; Luvas de látex para uso cirúrgico; Luvas de látex para uso veterinário; Luvas de borracha para uso cirúrgico; Luvas de proteção descartáveis para uso médico; Luvas de proteção para uso médico; Luvas de proteção para uso veterinário; Luvas descartáveis para uso cirúrgico; Luvas descartáveis para uso veterinário; Luvas para exames médicos; Luvas para uso no decurso de operações; Luvas para utilizar em hospitais; Luvas para uso dentário; Luvas para uso médico; Luvas para uso veterinário; Luvas de proteção para os cirurgiões usarem no decurso das intervenções cirúrgicas; Luvas de proteção para uso por profissionais de medicina; Luvas de proteção para uso por profissionais de medicina dentária; Luvas cirúrgicas; Vestuário, chapelaria e calçado para pessoal médico e doentes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole vestimentare de compresie pentru tratamente medicale; Mănuși din latex pentru examinare, pentru uz medical; Mănuși de latex de uz medical; Mănuși din cauciuc de uz medical; Mănuși din latex de uz stomatologic; Mănuși din latex de uz chirurgical; Mănuși din latex de uz veterinar; Mănuși din cauciuc de uz chirurgical; Mănuși de protecție de unică folosință, de uz medical; Mănuși de protecție de uz medical; Mănuși de protecție de uz veterinar; Mănuși de unică folosință de uz chirurgical; Mănuși de unică folosință de uz veterinar; Mănuși folosite la examinarea medicală; Mănuși de uz chirurgical; Mănuși de uz spitalicesc; Mănuși pentru uz stomatologic; Mănuși de uz medical; Mănuși pentru uz veterinar; Mănuși de protecție utilizate de chirurgi în timpul operațiilor; Mănuși de protecție utilizate de persoane care lucrează în domeniul medical; Mănuși de protecție utilizate de persoane care lucrează în domeniul stomatologic; Mănuși chirurgicale; Îmbrăcăminte, articole pentru acoperirea capului și încălțăminte pentru personal medical și pacienți.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tlakové odevy na lekárske účely; Latexové vyšetrovacie rukavice na lekárske použitie; Latexové rukavice na lekárske účely; Gumené rukavice na lekárske účely; Latexové rukavice na zubárske účely; Latexové rukavice na chirurgické účely; Latexové rukavice na zverolekárske účely; Gumené rukavice na chirurgické použitie; Jednorazové ochranné rukavice na lekárske účely; Ochranné rukavice na lekárske účely; Ochranné rukavice na zverolekárske účely; Jednorazové rukavice na chirurgické účely; Jednorazové rukavice na zverolekárske účely; Lekárske vyšetrovacie rukavice; Operačné rukavice; Rukavice používané v nemocniciach; Rukavice na stomatologické použitie; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Rukavice na veterinárne použitie; Ochranné rukavice používané chirurgmi počas operácií; Ochranné rukavice pre lekársky personál; Ochranné rukavice pre stomatologický personál; Chirurgické rukavice; Odevy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pre zdravotníckych pracovníkov a pacientov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kompresijska oblačila za medicinsko zdravljenje; Rokavice iz lateksa za pregledovanje za medicinsko uporabo; Rokavice iz lateksa za medicinsko uporabo; Gumijaste rokavice za medicinsko uporabo; Rokavice iz lateksa, za zobozdravstvene namene; Rokavice iz lateksa za kirurško uporabo; Rokavice iz lateksa, za veterinarsko uporabo; Gumijaste rokavice za kirurško uporabo; Zaščitne rokavice za enkratno uporabo za medicinske namene; Zaščitne rokavice za medicinsko uporabo; Zaščitne rokavice za veterinarsko uporabo; Rokavice za kirurške namene, za enkratno uporabo; Rokavice za veterinarske namene, za enkratno uporabo; Rokavice za zdravniške preglede; Rokavice, ki se uporabljajo med operacijami; Rokavice, ki se uporabljajo v bolnišnicah; Rokavice za zobozdravstveno uporabo; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Rokavice za veterinarsko uporabo; Zaščitne rokavice, ki jih uporabljajo kirurgi med operacijami; Zaščitne rokavice za medicinsko osebje; Zaščitne rokavice za zobozdravstveno osebje; Kirurške rokavice; Oblačila, pokrivala in obutev za medicinsko osebje in bolnike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tryckkläder för medicinska behandling; Undersökningshandskar i latex för medicinskt bruk; Latexhandskar för medicinskt bruk; Gummihandskar för medicinskt bruk; Latexhandskar för tandvård; Latexhandskar för kirurgiskt bruk; Latexhandskar för veterinärt bruk; Gummihandskar för kirurgiskt bruk; Engångsskyddshandskar för medicinska ändamål; Skyddshandskar för medicinskt bruk; Skyddshandskar för veterinärt bruk; Engångshandskar för kirurgiskt bruk; Engångshandskar för veterinärt bruk; Medicinska undersökningshandskar; Operationshandskar; Handskar för användning på sjukhus; Handskar för dental användning; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Handskar för veterinärt bruk; Skyddshandskar för användning av kirurger vid operationer; Skyddshandskar för användning av personer som arbetar inom sjukvård; Skyddshandskar för användning av personer som arbetar inom tandläkaryrket; Kirurgiska handskar; Kläder, huvudbonader och fotbeklädnader för medicinsk personal och patienter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Градинарски ръкавици; Ръкавици за козметична поддръжка на животни; Ръкавици за почистване на козината на домашни любимци; Ръкавици за полиране на обувки; Абразивни ръкавици за ексфолиране на кожата; Ръкавици за лъскане; Ръкавици за миене на коли; Ръкавици за бърсане на прах; Домакински ръкавици за почистване; Найлонови ръкавици за домакински цели; Памучни ръкавици за домакински цели; Гумени ръкавици за домашна употреба; Ръкавици за домакински цели; Абразивни ръкавици за почистване на зеленчуци.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zahradnické rukavice; Vyčesávací rukavice na zvířata; Vyčesávací rukavice na domácí mazlíčky; Rukavice na leštění obuvi; Brusné rukavice na exfoliaci kůže; Leštící rukavice; Rukavice na mytí automobilů; Rukavice na utírání prachu; Rukavice na úklid do domácnosti; Plastové domácí rukavice; Bavlněné rukavice k domácímu použití; Gumové rukavice pro použití v domácnosti; Rukavice pro použití v domácnosti; Rukavice se zdrsněným povrchem na čištění zeleniny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Handsker til havebrug; Handsker til pleje af dyr; Handsker til pleje af kæledyr; Skopudsningshandsker; Skrubbehandsker til skrubning af huden; Polerehandsker; Handsker til bilvask; Støvhandsker; Husholdningshandsker til rengøringsformål; Plastikhandsker til husholdningsbrug; Bomuldshandsker til husholdningsbrug; Gummihandsker til husholdningsbrug; Handsker til husholdningsbrug; Skrubbehandsker til grøntsager.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gartenhandschuhe; Tierpflegehandschuhe; Tierpflegehandschuhe; Schuhpolierhandschuhe; Hautpeeling-Handschuhe; Polierhandschuhe; Autowaschhandschuhe; Staubhandschuhe; Haushaltshandschuhe für Reinigungszwecke; Kunststoffhandschuhe für Haushaltszwecke; Haushaltshandschuhe aus Baumwolle; Gummihandschuhe für Haushaltszwecke; Haushaltshandschuhe; Gemüseputzhandschuhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Γάντια κηπουρικής· Γάντια για την περιποίηση ζώων· Γάντια καλλωπισμού κατοικίδιων ζώων· Γάντια χωρίς χωρίσματα για τα δάχτυλα για τη στίλβωση υποδημάτων· Γάντια απόξεσης για την απολέπιση του δέρματος· Γάντια στίλβωσης· Γάντια χωρίς χωρίσματα για τα δάκτυλα για πλύσιμο αυτοκινήτου· Γάντια για ξεσκόνισμα· Γάντια οικιακής χρήσης για σκοπούς καθαρισμού· Πλαστικά γάντια για οικιακή χρήση· Βαμβακερά γάντια για οικιακή χρήση· Γάντια οικιακής χρήσης από καουτσούκ· Γάντια οικιακής χρήσης· Λειαντικά γάντια για το τρίψιμο της επιφάνειας των λαχανικών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Gardening gloves; Animal grooming gloves; Pet grooming glove; Shoe polishing mitts; Abrasive mitts for scrubbing the skin; Polishing gloves; Car washing mitts; Dusting gloves; Household gloves for cleaning purposes; Household plastic gloves; Cotton gloves for household purposes; Rubber gloves for household use; Gloves for household purposes; Abrasive gloves for scrubbing vegetables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Guantes de jardinería; Guantes para el acicalamiento de animales; Guantes para acicalar a animales; Guantes para lustrar zapatos; Guantes exfoliantes para la piel; Guantes para lustrar; Guantes para lavar coches; Guantes para el polvo; Guantes domésticos para limpieza; Guantes domésticos de plástico; Guantes de algodón para uso doméstico; Guantes de goma para uso doméstico; Guantes para uso doméstico; Guantes abrasivos para limpiar verduras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Aiatöökindad; Loomade kammimiskindad; Kinnas lemmiklooma harjamiseks; Kingade poleerimiskindad; Nahakoorimiskindad; Poleerimiskindad, poleerkindad; Autopesukindad; Tolmupühkimiskindad; Majapidamiskindad puhastamiseks; Majapidamise plastkindad; Puuvillast majapidamiskindad; Majapidamises kasutatavad kummikindad; Majapidamiskindad; Köögiviljade puhastamise abrasiivkindad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Puutarhakäsineet; Käsineet eläinten harjaamiseen; Käsineet lemmikkieläinten turkinhoitoon; Kengänkiillotuskintaat; Kuorintahansikkaat ihon kuorintaan; Kiillotuskäsineet; Autonpesukintaat; Pölynpyyhintäkäsineet; Siivouskäsineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Muoviset kotitalouskäsineet; Puuvillakäsineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Kumiset talouskäsineet; Käsineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Hankauskäsineet vihannesten puhdistamiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Gants de jardinage; Gants de toilettage pour animaux; Gant pour le toilettage d’animaux de compagnie; Gants à lustrer pour chaussures; Gants exfoliant pour le gommage de la peau; Gants à polir; Gants pour le lavage de voitures; Gants à épousseter; Gants de nettoyage à usage ménager; Gants ménagers en plastique; Gants en coton à usage domestique; Gants en caoutchouc à usage domestique; Gants de ménage; Gants abrasifs pour nettoyer les légumes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Vrtlarske rukavice; Rukavice za njegu životinja; Rukavica za češljanje ljubimaca; Rukavice za poliranje cipela; Abrazivne rukavice za piling kože; Rukavice za poliranje; Rukavice za pranje automobila; Rukavice za čišćenje; Rukavice za čišćenje [za kućanstvo]; Plastične rukavice za kućanstvo; Pamučne rukavice za uporabu u kućanstvu; Gumene rukavice za kućanstvo; Rukavice za kućanstvo; Abrazivne rukavice za struganje povrća.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kertészeti kesztyűk; Állatfésülő kesztyűk; Kisállatfésülő kesztyűk; Cipőfényesítő kesztyűk; Dörzskesztyűk a bőr dörzsöléséhez; Kesztyűk fényesítéshez; Autómosó kesztyűk; Portörlő kesztyűk; Háztartási kesztyűk tisztításhoz; Műanyag kesztyűk háztartási célokra; Pamutkesztyűk háztartási célokra; Gumikesztyűk háztartási használatra; Kesztyűk háztartási használatra; Dörzskesztyűk zöldségek tisztításához.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Guanti da giardinaggio; Guanti per la tolettatura di animali; Guanto per la toelettatura di animali; Guanti per lucidare le scarpe; Guanti abrasivi per l'esfoliazione della pelle; Guanti per pulire; Guanti per il lavaggio delle auto; Guanti per spolverare; Guanti per pulire ad uso domestico; Guanti di plastica per la casa; Guanti di cotone per uso domestico; Guanti di gomma per uso domestico; Guanti per uso domestico; Guanti abrasivi per strofinare ortaggi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sodininkų pirštinės; Gyvūnų priežiūros pirštinės; Naminių gyvūnų priežiūros pirštinės; Batų blizginimo pirštinės; Abrazyvinės odos šveitimo pirštinės; Poliravimo pirštinės; Automobilių plovimo pirštinės; Dulkių valymo pirštinės; Buitinės pirštinės valymo reikmėms; Buitinės plastikinės pirštinės; Medvilninės pirštinės buities reikmėms; Guminės buitinės pirštinės; Buitinės pirštinės; Abrazyvinės pirštinės daržovėms valyti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dārza cimdi; Cimdi dzīvnieku kopšanai; Cimdi lolojumdzīvnieku kopšanai; Apavu spodrināšanas cimdi; Abrazīvi cimdi ādas beršanai; Spodrināšanas cimdi; Transportlīdzekļu mazgāšanas cimdi; Putekļu slaukāmie cimdi; Mājsaimniecībā izmantojamie tīrīšanas cimdi; Mājsaimniecībā izmantojamie plastmasas cimdi; Mājsaimniecībā izmantojami kokvilnas cimdi; Gumijas cimdi izmantošanai mājsaimniecībā; Cimdi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Abrazīvi cimdi dārzeņu tīrīšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ingwanti għal użu fil-ġonna; Ingwanti għat-tindif tas-sbuħija tal-annimali; Ingwanti għall-kura tal-annimali domestiċi; Ingwanti għall-illostrar taż-żraben; Ingwanti li jqaxxru, għat-tqaxxir tal-ġilda; Ingwanti għal-lustrar; Ingwanti għall-ħasil tal-karozzi; Ingwanti għat-tfarfir; Ingwanti domestiċi għall-użu fit-tindif; Ingwanti tal-plastik għall-użu domestiku; Ingwanti tal-qoton għall-użu fid-dar; Ingwanti tal-lastku għall-użu domestiku; Ingwanti għal skopijiet domestiċi; Ingwanti li joborxu għat-tqaxxir tal-ħaxix.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Handschoenen voor het tuinieren; Handschoenen voor dierenverzorging; Handschoen voor de verzorging van huisdieren; Schoenpoetshandschoenen; Scrub-handschoenen; Handschoenen voor het polijsten; Handschoenen voor het wassen van auto's; Afstofhandschoenen; Handschoenen voor de huishouding voor reinigingsdoeleinden; Plastic handschoenen voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Katoenen handschoenen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Rubberen handschoenen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Handschoenen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Schuurhandschoenen voor het schrobben van groenten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rękawice ogrodnicze; Rękawice do pielęgnacji zwierząt; Rękawice do pielęgnacji sierści zwierząt domowych; Rękawice do polerowania butów; Rękawiczki ścierne do peelingu skóry; Rękawice do polerowania; Rękawice do mycia samochodów; Rękawice do ścierania kurzu; Rękawice do czyszczenia do użytku domowego; Rękawice do prac domowych z tworzyw sztucznych; Rękawice bawełniane do celów domowych; Rękawice gumowe do użytku domowego; Rękawice do użytku domowego; Rękawice ścierające do szorowania warzyw.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Luvas para jardinagem; Luvas para limpeza de animais; Luva para cuidados de beleza de animais; Luvas para polir sapatos; Luvas abrasivas para esfoliação da pele; Luvas para polir; Luvas para lavagem de automóveis; Luvas para limpar o pó; Luvas domésticas para limpeza; Luvas de plástico para uso doméstico; Luvas de algodão para uso doméstico; Luvas de borracha para uso doméstico; Luvas para uso doméstico; Luvas abrasivas para lavagem de legumes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mănuși de grădinărit; Mănuși pentru îngrijirea animalelor; Mănușă de toaletat animale de companie; Mănuși pentru lustruit pantofii; Mănuși abrazive pentru exfolierea pielii; Mănuși de lustruit; Mănuși pentru spălarea mașinilor; Mănuși pentru șters praful; Mănuși pentru curățare sau pentru menaj; Mănuși din plastic de uz casnic; Mănuși de bumbac de uz casnic; Mănuși din cauciuc de uz casnic; Mănuși de menaj; Mănuși abrazive pentru curățat legume.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Záhradnícke rukavice; Rukavice na vyčesávanie srsti; Rukavice na vyčesávanie pre domáce zvieratá; Rukavice na leštenie topánok; Exfoliačné rukavice; Rukavice na leštenie; Rukavice na umývanie automobilov; Rukavice na utieranie prachu; Rukavice na čistenie domácností; Plastové rukavice do domácnosti; Bavlnené rukavice do domácnosti; Gumené rukavice pre použitie v domácnosti; Rukavice pre domácnosť; Abrazívne rukavice na čistenie zeleniny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vrtnarske rokavice; Rokavice za nego živali; Rokavice za nego hišnih ljubljenčkov; Rokavice za poliranje čevljev; Abrazivne rokavice za piling kože; Rokavice za poliranje; Rokavice za pranje avtomobila; Gospodinjske rokavice za brisanje prahu; Gospodinjske rokavice za čiščenje; Rokavice iz plastike za gospodinjske namene; Bombažne rokavice za gospodinjske namene; Gumijaste rokavice za gospodinjsko uporabo; Rokavice za gospodinjske namene; Rokavice za čiščenje zelenjave.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Trädgårdshandskar; Handskar för vård av djurpäls; Handskar för trimning av husdjur; Skoputsvantar; Skrubbvantar för huden; Polerhandskar; Tvätthandskar för biltvätt; Dammhandskar; Hushållshandskar för rengöringsändamål; Plasthandskar för hushållsändamål; Bomullshandskar för hushållsändamål; Gummihandskar för hushållsändamål; Handskar för hushållsändamål; Skrubbhandskar för grönsaker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>84848</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
