<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-18T08:29:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018340106</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018340106</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-11-18</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="1" status="1">Application filed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-11-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Yohii</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Капаци за компютърни клавиатури; Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Електронни писалки [визуални индикаторни устройства]; Интерфейс [за компютри]; Кодирани карти, магнитни; Измерватели; Капаци за мобилни телефони; Калъфи, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Калъфи за смартфони; Калъфи за таблети; Капаци за таблетни компютри; Връзки (аксесоари) за мобилни телефони; Магнитофони; Видеомагнетофони; Геодезични измервателни инструменти; Оптични фенери; Материали за електропроводи [проводници, кабели]; Войнишки каски; Шпионки [увеличаващи лещи] за врати; Калъфи за очила; Рамки за пенснета; Очила; Слънчеви очила; Апарати за ламбиране на яйца.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kryty na počítačové klávesnice; Periferní zařízení počítačů; Elektronická pera [vizualizační nástroje]; Rozhraní pro počítače; Kódované magnetické karty; Měřidla; Kryty na mobilní telefony; Obaly na mobilní telefony; Kryty na chytré telefony (smartphony); Pouzdra na tabletové počítače; Kryty pro tablety [počítače]; Šňůrky na mobilní telefony; Magnetofony; Videorekordéry; Geodetické nástroje; Optické lampy; Materiály pro elektrická vedení [vodiče, kabely]; Svářečské přilby; Dveřní kukátka [zvětšující čočky]; Pouzdra na brýle; Brýlové obroučky; Brýle; Sluneční brýle; Prosvěcovače vajec.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Covers til computertastaturer; Perifere enheder til computere; Penne, elektroniske [enheder til dataskærme]; Interfaces til computere; Kodede magnetiske kort; Måleredskaber; Mobiltelefonetuier; Etuier til mobiltelefoner; Covers til smartphones; Etuier til tablet-computere; Covers til tablet computere; Mobiltelefonremme; Båndoptagere; Videobåndoptagere; Landmålingsinstrumenter; Optiske lanterner; Materiel til elektriske hovedledninger [tråd, kabler]; Hjelme til beskyttelse ved lodning; Dørspioner [forstørrelseslinser] til anbringelse i døre; Etuier til briller; Brillestel; Briller; Solbriller; Klarelamper til gennemlysning af æg.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Abdeckungen für Computertastaturen; An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Elektronische Stifte für Bildschirmgeräte; Interfaces [Schnittstellengeräte oder -programme für Computer]; Kodierte Magnetkarten; Maße; Hüllen für Mobiltelefone; Etuis für Mobiltelefone; Hüllen für Smartphones; Etuis für Tablet-Computer; Hüllen für Tablet-Computer; Riemen für Mobiltelefone; Tonbandgeräte; Videorecorder; Landvermessungsinstrumente; Optische Lampen; Material für elektrische Leitungen [Drahte, Kabel]; Masken für Schweißer; Türgucker; Brillenetuis; Brillenfassungen, -gestelle; Brillen; Sonnenbrillen; Eierdurchleuchter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλύμματα για πληκτρολόγια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Ηλεκτρονικές γραφίδες [για μονάδες οπτικής παρουσίασης]· Διεπαφές (για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές)· Κωδικοποιημένες μαγνητικές κάρτες· Μέτρα προληπτικά· Καλύμματα κινητών τηλεφώνων· Θήκες για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Καλύμματα για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Θήκες για φορητούς ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Καλύμματα φορητών υπολογιστών-τύπου ταμπλέτας· Λουράκια για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Συσκευές καταγραφής με μαγνητική ταινία· Μαγνητοσκόπια· Τοπογραφικά όργανα· Οπτικοί λαμπτήρες· Υλικά για δίκτυα ηλεκτρισμού [σύρματα, καλώδια]· Συγκόλληση (Μάσκες για -)· Μάτι πορτών· Επιρρίνιων γυαλιών οράσεως θήκες· Σκελετοί γυαλιών· Διόπτρες· Γυαλιά ηλίου· Ωροσκόπια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Covers for computer keyboards; Computer peripheral devices; Electronic pens; Interfaces for computers; Magnetically encoded cards; Measures; Cell phone covers; Cell phone cases; Protective covers for smartphones; Cases for tablet computers; Protective covers for tablet computers; Cell phone straps; Tape recorders; Video recorders; Surveying instruments; Optical lamps; Materials for electricity mains [wires, cables]; Solderers' helmets; Peepholes [magnifying lenses] for doors; Pince-nez cases; Spectacle frames; Eyeglasses; Sunglasses; Egg-candlers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Fundas para teclados de ordenador; Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Lápices electrónicos para unidades de visualización; Interfaces [informática]; Tarjetas magnéticas codificadas; Medidores; Fundas para teléfonos móviles; Estuches adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Carcasas para teléfonos inteligentes; Estuches para ordenadores tipo tablilla; Carcasas para tabletas electrónicas; Cordones para teléfonos celulares; Grabadoras de cinta magnética; Grabadoras de vídeo; Instrumentos de agrimensura; Lámparas ópticas; Material para conducciones eléctricas [hilos, cables]; Caretas para soldar; Mirillas ópticas para puertas; Estuches para gafas; Monturas de gafas; Gafas [óptica]; Gafas de sol; Ovoscopios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutiklaviatuuride katted; Arvutite välisseadmed; Elektronpliiatsid [kuvarimanused]; Liidesed arvutitele; Kodeeritud magnetkaardid; Mõõtevahendid; Mobiiltelefonide katted; Mobiiltelefonivutlarid; Nutitelefonide katted; Tahvelarvutite vutlarid; Tahvelarvutite ümbrised; Mobiiltelefonide rihmad; Magnetofonid; Videomagnetofonid; Geodeesiariistad; Optilised lambid; Elektriliinimaterjalid [juhtmed, kaablid]; Keevitajate kaitsekiivrid; Uksesilmad; Prillitoosid; Prilliraamid; Prillid [optika]; Päikeseprillid; Ovoskoobid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneen näppäimistösuojukset; Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Kynät, elektroniset; Liitäntälaitteet tietokoneisiin; Koodatut magneettikortit; Mitat; Matkapuhelinten kotelot; Matkapuhelinkotelot; Älypuhelinten suojukset; Taulutietokoneille tarkoitetut kotelot; Tablettitietokoneiden suojakotelot; Matkapuhelimen hihnat; Ääninauhurit; Videonauhurit; Maanmittauslaitteet; Optiset lyhdyt; Sähköjakeluverkkokaapelit; Juottajankypärät; Ovisilmälinssit; Silmälasikotelot; Silmälasinkehykset; Silmälasit; Aurinkolasit; Munien läpivalaisulaitteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Housses pour claviers d’ordinateurs; Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Crayons électroniques pour unités d'affichage visuel; Interfaces [informatique]; Cartes magnétiques codées; Mesures; Housses pour téléphones portables; Étuis pour téléphones portables; Coques pour smartphones; Etuis pour tablettes électroniques; Coques pour tablettes électroniques; Cordonnets pour téléphones mobiles; Enregistreurs à bande magnétique; Magnétoscopes; Instruments d'arpentage; Lampes optiques; Matériel pour conduites d'électricité [fils, câbles]; Masques de soudeurs; Judas optiques pour portes; Étuis à lunettes; Montures de lunettes; Lunettes [optique]; Lunettes de soleil; Mire-œufs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pokrovi za računalne tipkovnice; Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Svjetlosne olovke; Sučelja za računala; Kodirane magnetne kartice; Mjerila; Navlake za mobitele; Futrole prilagođene za mobilne telefone; Navlake za pametne telefone; Futrole za tablet računala; Futrole za tablet računala; Trake za mobilne telefone; Magnetofoni; Magnetoskopi; Instrumenti za geodetsko mjerenje; Optičke svjetiljke; Materijali za električne mreže [žice, kablovi]; Maske za zavarivače; Vrata [prozorčići s povećalom na vratima]; Navlake za cvikere; Okviri za naočale; Naočale; Sunčane naočale; Ovoskopi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tokok számítógépek billentyűzetéhez; Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Fényceruzák vizuális kijelzőkhöz, displayekhez; Számítógép interfészek; Kódolt mágneskártyák; Mérőeszközök, mértékek; Tokok mobiltelefonokhoz; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított tokok; Tokok okostelefonokhoz; Tokok táblagépekhez; Táblagép tokok; Szíjak, pántok mobiltelefonokhoz; Magnetofonok; Videomagnók, képmagnók; Földmérő eszközök; Optikai lámpák; Anyagok elektromos hálózatokhoz, fővezetékekhez [huzalok, kábelek]; Hegesztőpajzsok; Kémlelőnyílások [nagyítólencsék] ajtókra; Szemüvegtokok; Szemüvegkeretek; Szemüvegek; Napszemüvegek; Tojáslámpázók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fodere per tastiere di computer; Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Matite elettroniche per unità di visualizzazione; Interfacce [informatica]; Tessere magnetiche codificate; Misure; Custodie per telefoni cellulari; Custodie adattate per telefoni cellulari; Copertine per smartphone; Custodie per tablet; Covers per tablet; Cinghie per cellulari; Registratori a nastro magnetico; Magnetoscopi; Strumenti per rilevamenti topografici; Lampade ottiche; Materiale per condotte per l'elettricità [fili, cavi]; Maschere per saldatori; Spioncini ottici per porte; Astucci per occhiali; Montature di occhiali; Occhiali [ottica]; Occhiali da sole; Sperauova.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kompiuterių klaviatūrų dangteliai; Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Elektroniniai rašikliai [rodymo įtaisai]; Sąsajos įrenginiai [kompiuteriams]; Koduotosios magnetinės kortos; Matai; Mobiliųjų telefonų dangteliai; Mobiliesiems telefonams pritaikyti dėklai; Išmaniųjų telefonų dangteliai; Planšetinių kompiuterių dangteliai; Planšetinių kompiuterių dangteliai; Mobiliųjų telefonų dirželiai; Juostiniai įrašymo aparatai; Vaizdo magnetofonai; Geodezijos prietaisai; Optiniai žibintai; Elektros linijų medžiagos [laidai, kabeliai]; Lituotojų šalmai; Durų akutės [didinamieji lęšiai]; Akinių įmautės; Akinių rėmai; Akiniai; Saulės akiniai; Kiaušinių tikrinimo prietaisai [ovoskopai].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pārsegi datoru tastatūrām; Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Elektroniskie zīmuļi (displeju piederumi); Saskarnes programmas un ierīces datoriem; Kodētas magnētiskās kartes; Mēri; Mobilo telefonu vāciņi; Mobilo tālruņu futrāļi; Viedtālruņu vāciņi; Planšetdatoru futrāļi; Planšetdatoru vāciņi un apvalki; Mobilo telefonu aukliņas; Magnetofoni; Videomagnetofoni; Ģeodēzijas instrumenti; Optisko šķiedru lampas; Elektrotīklu materiāli (vadi, kabeļi); Metinātāju aizsargķiveres; Durvju actiņas (optiskās); Briļļu maki; Briļļu rāmji; Brilles; Saulesbrilles; Ovoskopi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kavers għal tastieri tal-kompjuter; Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Pinen elettroniċi; Punti ta' interazzjoni għall-kompjuters; Kards manjetiċi kkodifikati; Kejl; Għata għat-telefowns ċellulari; Kaxxetti adattati għat-telefowns ċellulari; Kavers għal smartfowns; Kaxxetti għal kompjuters stil tablet; Għata għall-kompjuters tablets; Ċineg tat-telefons ċellulari; Tagħmir għal reġistrazzjoni fuq tejp; Reġistraturi tal-vidjo; Strumenti għal stħarriġ wiesa'; Fanali ottiċi; Materjali għall-mejns tal-elettriku (linji); Elmi għall-welders; Toqob żgħar [b'lentijiet li jkabbru] biex tittawwal minnhom għall-bibien; Kontenituri tan-nuċċalijiet; Frejms għan-nuċċalijiet; Nuċċalijiet; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Eżaminaturi tal-bajd kontra d-dawl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hoezen voor computertoetsenborden; Computerrandapparatuur; Lichtpennen; Interfaces [informatica]; Gecodeerde magneetkaarten; Maten; Hoesjes voor mobiele telefoons; Hoesjes voor mobiele telefoons; Hoezen voor smartphones; Hoezen voor tablets; Hoesjes voor tabletcomputers; Koordjes voor mobiele telefoons; Bandrecorders; Videorecorders; Landmeetkundige instrumenten; Optische lampen; Materiaal voor elektrische leidingen [draden, kabels]; Lasmaskers; Judassen [kijkglaasjes voor deuren]; Brillenkokers; Brilmonturen; Brillen [optiek]; Zonnebrillen; Doorlichtapparaten voor eieren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Osłony na klawiatury komputerowe; Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Elektroniczne pióra [ekranopisy]; Interfejsy komputerowe; Kodowane karty magnetyczne; Miary; Osłony na telefony komórkowe; Futerały dopasowane do telefonów komórkowych; Pokrowce na smartfony; Etui do tabletów; Pokrowce do tabletów; Paski do telefonów komórkowych; Magnetofony; Magnetowidy; Przyrządy do pomiarów geodezyjnych; Lampy optyczne; Materiały na przewody instalacji elektrycznych [kable]; Przyłbice do spawania; Wizjery do drzwi [judasze]; Etui na okulary; Oprawki do okularów; Okulary; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne; Owoskopy [prześwietlarki jaj].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Capas para teclados de computadores; Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Canetas eletrónicas [canetas digitais] para unidades de visualização; Interfaces [informática]; Cartões magnéticos codificados; Medidores; Capas para telemóveis; Bolsas adaptadas para telemóveis; Coberturas para smartphones; Malas concebidas para computadores "tablet"; Capas para computadores tablet; Correias para telefones móveis; Gravadores ou registadores de fita magnética; Gravadores de vídeo; Instrumentos para agrimensura; Lâmpadas óticas; Materiais para condução elétrica [fios, cabos]; Máscaras de soldadores; Visores para portas; Estojos para óculos; Armações de óculos; Óculos [ótica]; Óculos de sol; Ensaiadores [aparelhos para o controlo] de ovos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Huse pentru tastaturi de calculator; Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Creioane electronice [pentru unități de afișaj vizual]; Interfețe [informatică]; Carduri magnetice codate; Măsuri; Carcase pentru telefoane mobile; Etuiuri pentru telefoane mobile; Huse pentru telefoane inteligente; Huse pentru calculatoare tabletă; Huse pentru tablete; Curele pentru telefonul mobil; Magnetofoane; Magnetoscoape; Instrumente topografice; Lanterne optice; Materiale pentru rețeaua de electricitate [fire, cabluri]; Măști de sudură; Vizoare optice pentru uși; Tocuri pentru ochelari fără brațe; Rame de ochelari fără brațe; Ochelari; Ochelari de soare; Ovoscoape.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kryty pre počítačové klávesnice; Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Elektronické perá (vizuálne zobrazovacie zariadenia); Počítačové rozhrania; Kódované magnetické karty; Mierky; Obaly na mobilné telefóny; Puzdrá na mobilné telefóny; Kryty na smartfóny; Puzdrá na tabletové počítače; Obaly na elektronické tablety; Šnúrky na mobilné telefóny; Magnetofóny; Videorekordéry; Geodetické nástroje; Optické lampy; Materiály na elektrické vedenie (drôty, káble); Zváračské kukly; Dverové priezory; Puzdrá na okuliare; Rámy na okuliare; Okuliare; Slnečné okuliare; Ovoskopy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Ovitki za računalniške tipkovnice; Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Elektronska peresa [za optično čitanje podatkov]; Vmesniki za računalnike; Kodirane magnetne kartice; Mere; Ovitki za mobilne telefone; Etuiji za mobilne telefone; Ohišja za pametne telefone; Etuiji za tablične računalnike; Ovitki za tablične računalnike; Trakovi za prenosne telefone; Magnetofoni; Videorekorderji; Instrumenti za merjenje zemljišča; Optične svetilke; Materiali za električno napeljavo [žice, kabli]; Čelade za varjenje; Kukala s povečevalnim steklom za vrata; Etuiji za očala; Okvirji za očala; Očala; Sončna očala; Ovoskopi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Överdrag för tangentbord till datorer; Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Elektroniska pennor [visuella visningsenheter]; Gränssnitt (för datorer); Magnetiska kodade kort; Mått; Mobiletelefonfodral; Fodral anpassade för mobiltelefoner; Fodral för smartphones; Fodral för surfplattor; Fodral till surfplattor; Band för mobiltelefoner; Bandinspelare; Videoinspelare; Geodetiska instrument; Optiska lampor; Material för elektriska huvudledningar [tråd, kablar]; Svetshjälmar; Titthål [förstoringslinser] för dörrar; Glasögonfodral; Glasögonbågar; Glasögon; Solglasögon; Äggenomlysningsapparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>96576</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
